<?xml-model href="../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <artist>Childish Gambino</artist>
        <year>2011</year>
        <title>Outside</title>
        <album>Camp</album>
        <trackNumber>1</trackNumber>
    </metadata>
    <verse vocals="Childish Gambino" mood="sad" tone="negative">
        <line>I used to dream every night, now I never dream at all</line>
        <line>I'm hopin' that it's cause I'm livin' everything I want</line>
        <topic type="poverty">
            <line>I used to wake up in a bed between my mom and aunt</line>
            <line>Playing with this Land Before Time toy from Pizza Hut</line>
            <line>My dad works nights, putting on a stone face</line>
            <line>He's saving up so we can get our own place</line>
            <line>In the projects, man that sounds fancy to me</line>
        </topic>
        <line>They called me "fat nose," my mom say, "You handsome to me"</line>
        <line>Mrs. Glover ma'am, your son is so advanced</line>
        <line>But he's acting up in class and keeps peeing in his pants</line>
        <line>And I just wanna fit in, but nobody was helping me out</line>
        <line>They talking hood shit and I ain't know what that was about</line>
        <line>Cause hood shit and black shit is super different</line>
        <line>So I'm talking hood shit and cool it now like New Edition</line>
        <line>Mom and dad wouldn't listen</line>
        <line>They left the Bronx so I wouldn't be that</line>
        <line>All their friends in NY deal crack</line>
        <line>It's weird, you think that they'd be proud of 'em</line>
        <line>But when you leave the hood</line>
        <line>They think that you look down on 'em</line>
        <line>The truth is we still struggle on a different plane</line>
        <topic type="poverty">
            <line>7 dollars an hour, WIC vouchers, it's all the same</line>
        </topic>
        <line>Facebook messaging hopin' that could patch up shit</line>
        <line>But all they get now is, "Can your son read this script?"</line>
    </verse>
    <chorus vocals="Childish Gambino" mood="ambiguous" tone="positive">
        <line>There's a world we can visit if we go outside</line>
        <line>Outside, outside—we can follow the road</line>
        <line>There's a world we can visit if we go outside</line>
        <line>Outside, outside—no one knows</line>
        <line>There's a world we can visit if we go outside</line>
        <line>Outside, outside—we can follow the road</line>
        <line>There's a world we can visit if we go outside</line>
        <line>Outside, outside—no one knows</line>
    </chorus>
    <verse vocals="Childish Gambino" mood="sad" tone="negative">
        <topic type="family">
            <line>Yeah, Dad lost his job, mama worked at Mrs. Winner's</line>
            <line>Gun pulled in her face, she still made dinner</line>
            <line>“Donald, watch the meter so they don’t turn the lights off"</line>
            <line>Workin' two jobs so I can get into that white school</line>
        </topic>
        <line>And I hate it there</line>
        <line>They all make fun of my clothes and wanna touch my hair</line>
        <topic type="family">
            <line>And my uncle on that stuff that got my grandma shook</line>
            <line>Drug dealers roughed him up and stole his address book</line>
            <line>He’s supposed to pay ‘em back</line>
            <line>He owe 'em money but his bank account is zero</line>
            <line>So my mama made us sleep with Phillips heads</line>
            <line>Under the pillow, like that would do somethin'</line>
            <line>But she’s got six kids, she’s gotta do somethin'</line>
            <line>She don’t want me in a lifestyle like my cousin</line>
            <line>And he mad cause his father ain’t around</line>
            <line>He lookin' at me now, like</line>
            <line>"Why you so fuckin' lucky? I had a father too</line>
            <line>But he ain’t around, so I'ma take it out on you"</line>
            <line>We used to say "I love you," now we only think that shit</line>
            <line>It feels weird that you’re the person I took sink baths with</line>
            <line>Street took you over, I want my cousin back</line>
            <line>The world sayin' what you are</line>
            <line>Because you’re young and black, don't believe 'em</line>
            <line>You're still that kid who kept the older boys</line>
            <line>From teasin', for some reason</line>
        </topic>
    </verse>
    <chorus vocals="Childish Gambino" mood="ambiguous" tone="positive">
        <line>There's a world we can visit if we go outside</line>
        <line>Outside, outside—we can follow the road</line>
        <line>There's a world we can visit if we go outside</line>
        <line>Outside, outside—no one knows</line>
        <line>There's a world we can visit if we go outside</line>
        <line>Outside, outside—we can follow the road</line>
        <line>There's a world we can visit if we go outside</line>
        <line>Outside, outside—no one knows</line>
    </chorus>
    <outro vocals="Childish Gambino" mood="sad" tone="positive">
        <line>Can you hear me now?</line>
        <line>Can you hear me now?</line>
        <line>Oh, help us Lord</line>
        <line>Oh, I'm screamin' baby, baby</line>
    </outro>
</song>
