<?xml-model href="../../../../hip-hop-humanities/relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <artist>Childish Gambino</artist>
        <year>2011</year>
        <title>Bonfire</title>
        <album>Camp</album>
        <trackNumber>3</trackNumber>
    </metadata>
    <verse vocals="Childish Gammbino" mood="confident" tone="positive">
        <line>Okay, it's Childish Gambino, homegirl drop it like the NASDAQ</line>
        <line>Move white girls like there's coke up my asscrack</line>
        <line>Move black girls 'cause, man, fuck it, I'll do either</line>
        <line>I love pussy, I love bitches, dude, I should be runnin’ PETA</line>
        <line>In Adidas, with some short shorts, B-O-O all over me</line>
        <topic type="money">
            <line>My green is where it's supposed to be, your green is in my grocery</line>
        </topic>
        <line>This Asian dude, I stole his girl, and now he got that Kogi beef</line>
        <line>My dick is like an accent mark, it's all about the over E's</line>
        <line>Hot like a parked car</line>
        <line>I sound weird like "nigga" with a hard 'R'</line>
        <line>Fly like the logo on my cousin's 440</line>
        <line>Eatin' Oreos like these white girls that blow me</line>
        <line>Vodka for my ladies, whiskey for a grown man</line>
        <line>Hangin' in the islands, lookin' for Earl like Toejam</line>
        <line>I made the beat retarded, so I'm callin' it a slow jam</line>
        <line>Butcher and I know it, man, kill beef, go ham</line>
        <line>These rappers are afraid of him</line>
        <line>'Cause I'm a beast, bitch, "grrr", Invader Zim</line>
        <line>Gambino is a call girl, fuck you, pay me</line>
        <line>Brand new whip for these niggas like slavery</line>
        <line>Told me I was awful and that shit did not faze me</line>
        <line>Tell me how I suck again, my memory is hazy</line>
        <line>“You're my favorite rapper now”, yeah, dude, I better be</line>
        <line>Or you can fuckin, kiss my ass, Human Centipede</line>
        <line>You wanna see my girl? I ain't that dumb</line>
        <line>You wanna see my girl? Check Maxim</line>
        <line>"Man, why does every black actor gotta rap some?”</line>
        <line>I don't know, all I know is I'm the best one</line>
    </verse>
    <chorus vocals="Childish Gammbino" mood="confident" tone="negative">
        <line>It's a bonfire, turn the lights out</line>
        <line>I'm burnin' everything you mothafuckas talk about</line>
        <line>It's a bonfire, turn the lights out</line>
        <line>I'm burnin' everything you mothafuckas talk about</line>
    </chorus>
    <verse vocals="Childish Gammbino" mood="confident" tone="positive">
        <line>You know these rapper dudes talk shit, start killin'</line>
        <line>Fuck that, got goons like an archvillain</line>
        <line>I'm from the South, ain't got no accent, don't know why</line>
        <line>So this rap is child's play, I do my name like Princess Di</line>
        <line>Yeah, they say they want the realness, rap about my real life</line>
        <line>Told me I should just quit, "First of all, you talk white</line>
        <line>Second off, you talk like you haven't given up yet"</line>
        <line>Rap's stepfather, yeah, you hate me but you will respect</line>
        <line>I put in work, ask Ludwig</line>
        <line>Put my soul on the track like shoes did</line>
        <line>Played this for my cousin, now he can't even think straight</line>
        <line>Black and white music? Now, nigga, that's a mixtape</line>
        <line>Shoutout to my blerds, they represent the realness</line>
        <line>Shoutout to Gambino Girls, my dick is in the building</line>
        <line>I know you hate me 'cause your little cousin play me out</line>
        <line>I like black girls who nerdy but when they dance they be sayin' "Ow"</line>
        <line>I'm sorry for who followed me</line>
        <line>Chillin' with a Filipina at your local Jollibee</line>
        <line>Yeah, I'm in her ass like sodomy</line>
        <line>So if you see my hand under the table, don't bother me</line>
        <line>I don't talk soft, that's that other guy</line>
        <line>I'm screamin' "What the fuck is up?" like I ain't seen the sky</line>
        <line>The shit I'm doin' this year? Insanity</line>
        <line>Made the beat then murdered it, Casey Anthony</line>
        <line>These rappers don't know what to do</line>
        <line>'Cause all I did was act me, like a Looney Tune</line>
        <line>And I'll give you all of me until there’s nothing left</line>
        <line>I swear this summer will be summer Camp, bitch</line>
    </verse>
</song>
