<?xml-model href="../../../../hip-hop-humanities/relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <artist>ASAP Rocky</artist>
        <year>2013</year>
        <title>Hell</title>
        <featuredArtist>Haim</featuredArtist>
        <album>Long. Live. ASAP</album>
        <trackNumber>4</trackNumber>
    </metadata>
    <intro vocals="ASAP Rocky" mood="ambiguous" tone="null">
        <line>Clams Casino, nigga</line>
        <line>A$AP</line>
    </intro>
    <verse vocals="ASAP Rocky" mood="angry" tone="negative">
        <line>Mr. Pistol Popper, Flacko locked and loaded</line>
        <line>Life's a bitch and she pussy pop, know why? Cause I got her open</line>
        <line>That pussy soaking, fuck is you promoting?</line>
        <line>Yeah, you claim you rage, you hating like you live in Oakland</line>
        <line>All my rap town niggas with the roof back</line>
        <line>Introduce you niggas to the new swag</line>
        <line>Make you say a nigga blew up too fast</line>
        <line>Fuck I'm 'sposed to do with all this new ass?</line>
        <line>Fuck I'm 'sposed to do with all this new cash?</line>
        <line>Thousand dollar drawers just to hold my balls</line>
        <line>All I ever do is let my jewels sag</line>
        <line>Pac gone, but the "Juice" back</line>
        <line>Get your popcorn, juice, snacks</line>
        <line>It's a movie nigga, with a new cast</line>
        <line>Get the news flash, that the truth back</line>
        <line>This is boom bap, mixed with new raps</line>
        <line>Look at all the niggas that I blew past</line>
        <line>Hood by Air, to the do-rag</line>
        <line>Nigga make way for the new jacks</line>
    </verse>
    <verse vocals="ASAP Rocky" mood="ambiguous" tone="null">
        <line>Yea, uh</line>
        <line>Yea, uh</line>
        <line>Uhh</line>
        <line>Yea, yea</line>
        <line>Uhh</line>
        <line>Uh, uhh</line>
    </verse>
    <verse vocals="ASAP Rocky" mood="cynical" tone="negative">
        <line>It's Mr. Pistol Popper screaming, "Fuck a copper"</line>
        <line>I just bought a crispy choppa, finna fuck your block up, blocka!</line>
        <line>Even cracked the pavement that's for niggas hating</line>
        <line>I been impatiently waiting to show you niggas Satan</line>
        <line>All this talk of Illuminati ain't got a clue about me</line>
        <line>Bitch, I'm Trillmaluminati and got my crew behind me</line>
        <line>Shooters round me, keep them looters round me</line>
        <line>Keep a tool around me, it'll keep you fools from round me</line>
        <line>Couple of them dudes surround me</line>
        <line>With a gat, with a strap in a backpack</line>
        <line>When they cap cap, leave you flat, better back back</line>
        <line>On a fast track, ratatat, nigga that's that</line>
        <line>Nigga pass that, finna ash, where the hash at</line>
        <line>Got a Kat Stacks with a ass, finna smash that</line>
        <line>Make 'em catch that, A$AP, then I pass that</line>
        <line>Off to my niggas then she ask, "Where the cash at?"</line>
        <line>I see dead people, I need dead people</line>
        <line>Lord Pretty Flacko, bitch, I behead people</line>
        <line>Kneel and kiss the ring, all hail the King</line>
        <line>Long Live A$AP put that on everything</line>
    </verse>
    <outro vocals="Haim" mood="ambiguous" tone="neutral">
        <line>Alright, mothafucka</line>
        <line>Alright, A$AP</line>
        <line>All you need is love</line>
        <line>All you need is love</line>
        <line>All you need is love</line>
        <line>All you need is love</line>
        <line>All you need is love</line>
    </outro>
</song>
