<?xml-model href="file:/C:/Users/Ashley/Desktop/New%20folder/relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <artist>ASAP Rocky</artist>
        <year>2013</year>
        <title>Phoenix</title>
        <album>Long. Live. ASAP</album>
    </metadata>
    <verse vocals="ASAP Rocky" mood="cynical" tone="negative">
        <line>Bloody ink on my pad spelled suicide</line>
        <topic type="death">
            <line>Michael Jackson even passed cause you scrutinized</line>
        </topic>
        <line>Fuck Illuminati lies, say I'm lucified</line>
        <line>Baptized in the gutter, motherfucker you decide</line>
        <line>Cause the ride come with doors that be suicide</line>
        <line>Or the thighs on my whores, they be super-sized</line>
        <line>Good and bad having wars, nigga, choose a side</line>
        <line>Now all hail to the Lord like you do to God</line>
        <line>Who am I? Lord Flacko</line>
        <line>Painting vivid pictures, call me Basquiat, Picasso</line>
        <line>Capo Head Hancho, now my following's colossal</line>
        <line>Ain't no boxer, Pacquiao, but got the chopper todo caso</line>
        <line>It's like you heard God spoke, I seen the ghetto gospel</line>
        <line>The choir like my reefer and the preacher got my eyes low</line>
        <topic type="drugs">
            <line>Sister Mary Jane to make me sleep from singing high notes</line>
        </topic>
        <line>The bible or the rifle, goodnight folks</line>
    </verse>
    <verse vocals="ASAP Rocky" mood="cynical" tone="negative">
        <line>Bloody ink on my pen spelled suicide</line>
        <topic type="death">
            <line>Kurt Cobain even died cause you scrutinize</line>
        </topic>
        <line>It's a fine line between truth and lies</line>
        <topic type="religion">
            <line>Jesus Christ never lied, still was crucified</line>
        </topic>
        <line>That's why I never judge another nigga</line>
        <line>Life's a bitch, but that bitch in love with other niggas</line>
        <line>3 to a bed, sheets, no covers nigga</line>
        <line>Dirty kitchen, no supper in the cupboards nigga</line>
        <line>Sucker niggas, wassup with niggas?</line>
        <line>So my new attitude is like "Fuck them niggas!"</line>
        <line>I grew up with niggas but don't fuck with niggas</line>
        <line>I don't trust them niggas, ain't got no love for niggas</line>
        <line>Had the gold grills shining like them southern niggas</line>
        <line>Kept it trilla, now the whole world fuckin' with us</line>
        <line>Meanwhile, you treated all of us like other niggas</line>
        <line>Now your world is in my palm, take cover niggas</line>
    </verse>
    <bridge vocals="ASAP Rocky" mood="sad" tone="neutral">
        <line>If I shall ever fall, Lord pick me up</line>
        <line>Ever since a baby, two deuce in sippy cups</line>
        <line>Ever since them diapers and my zip-me-ups</line>
        <line>Now I'm walking on my own, y'all, wish me luck</line>
    </bridge>
    <outro vocals="ASPA Rocky" mood="anxious" tone="negative">
        <line>Where do we lie</line>
        <line>Tell me where do we stand</line>
        <line>Where do we go</line>
        <line>It's all part of the plan</line>
        <line>Where do we lie</line>
        <line>Tell me where do we stand</line>
        <line>Where do we go</line>
        <line>It's all part of the plan</line>
    </outro>
</song>
