<?xml-model href="../../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
        <metadata>
            <artist>J.Cole</artist>
            <year>2010</year>
            <title>In the Morning</title>
            <featuredArtist>Drake</featuredArtist>
            <album>Friday Night Lights</album>
            <trackNumber>10</trackNumber>
        </metadata>

<verse vocals="J_Cole" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<line>Baby, you summertime fine</line>
<line>I let you get on top, I be the underline, I'm</line>
<line>Tryna get beside you like the number nine, dime</line>
<line>You fine as hell</line>
<line>I guess I met you for a reason, only time can tell</line>
<line>But well, I'm wonderin' what type of shit you wantin'</line>
<line>Do you like the finer things or you a simple woman?</line>
<topic type="drugs"><line>Would you drink with a nigga? Do you smoke weed?</line></topic>
<topic type="drugs"><line>Don't be ashamed, it ain't no thing, I used to blow trees</line></topic>
<line>Gettin' lifted, I quit but shit, I might get high with you</line>
<line>It's only fittin' 'cause I'm lookin' super fly with you</line>
<line>A flower, you are powerful, you do somethin' to me</line>
<line>'Cause girl, I caught the vibe like you threw somethin' to me</line>
<line>So I threw 'em back, now all my niggas hollerin', “Who was that?”</line>
<line>“Oh boy, she bad nigga, what you 'bout to do with that?”</line>
<line>I'm finna take you home, just sip a little Patron</line>
<line>Now we zonin', baby you so fine</line>
</verse>

<chorus vocals="J_Cole" mood="determined" tone="positive">
<line>And can I hit it in the mornin'?</line>
<line>Can I hit it in the mornin'?</line>
<line>And can I hit it in the mornin'?</line>
<line>The Sun risin' while you moanin'</line>
<line>And can I hit it in the mornin'?</line>
<line>Can I hit it in the mornin'?</line>
<line>And can I hit it in the mornin'?</line>
<line>The Sun risin' while you moanin'</line>
</chorus>
    
<verse vocals="Drake" mood="null" tone="null">
<line>Uh, baby, you wintertime cold</line>
<line>The night is still young, drink that dinner wine slow</line>
<line>I'm tryna make the goosebumps on your inner thigh show</line>
<line>I'll let you beat me there as far as finish lines go</line>
<line>Yeah, and if you gotta leave for work</line>
<line>I'll be right here in the same bed that you left me in</line>
<line>I love thick women 'cause my aunt she rode equestrian</line>
<line>I used to go to the stables and get them kids to bet me</line>
<line>And I would always ride the stallions whenever she let me</line>
<line>I'm jokin', I mean that thing is pokin'</line>
<line>I mean you kinda like that girl that's in the US Open</line>
<line>I mean I got this hidden agenda that you provokin'</line>
<line>I got bath water that you can soak in, things I could do with lotion</line>
<line>Don't need a towel, we could dry off in the covers</line>
<line>And when you think you like it, I promise you gonna love it</line>
<line>Yeah, when lights comin' through the drapes and we both yawnin'</line>
<line>I roll over and ask if I can hit it in the mornin'</line>
</verse>

<chorus vocals="Drake" mood="null" tone="null">
<line>Yeah, can I hit it in the mornin'?</line>
<line>Yeah, can I hit it in the mornin'?</line>
<line>Yeah, the Sun risin' while you moanin', baby</line>
<line>Can I hit it in the mornin', uh?</line>
<line>Can I hit it in the mornin', yeah?</line>
<line>Can I hit it in the mornin'?</line>
<line>The Sun risin' while you moanin'</line>
</chorus>
    
<verse vocals="J_Cole" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<topic type="religion"><line>Hey, God bless the child that can hold his own</line></topic>
<topic type="religion"><line>God bless the woman that can hold Patron</line></topic>
<topic type="religion"><line>God bless her homegirl that drove us home</line></topic>
<line>No strings attached like a cordless phone</line>
<line>You see my intentions with you was clear</line>
<line>I'm learnin' not to judge a woman by the shit that she wear</line>
<line>Therefore you shouldn't judge a nigga off the shit that you hear</line>
<line>Get all defensive, apprehensive, all because my career</line>
<line>To be fair, I know we barely know each other and yeah</line>
<line>Somehow I wound up in your bed so where we headed from here?</line>
<line>Just say you're scared if you're scared</line>
<line>But if you through frontin', we can do somethin'</line>
<line>And you know just what I'm talkin' about</line>
<line>Tomorrow you'll be callin' out</line>
<line>'Cause tonight we gettin' right into the wee morn'</line>
<line>Cook a nigga breakfast after sex is like a reward</line>
<line>Then I go my own way, you think about me all day</line>
<line>That's just a warnin'</line>
</verse>

<chorus vocals="Drake" mood="null" tone="null">
<line>And can I hit it in the mornin'?</line>
<line>Can I hit it in the mornin'?</line>
<line>Can I hit it in the mornin'?</line>
<line>The Sun risin' while you moanin'</line>
<line>Can I hit it in the mornin'?</line>
<line>Can I hit it in the mornin'?</line>
<line>And can I hit it in the mornin'?</line>
<line>The Sun risin' while you moanin', yeah</line>
</chorus>
</song>