<?xml-model href="../../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <artist>J.Cole</artist>
        <year>2011</year>
        <title>Who Dat</title>
        <featuredArtist>Andre 3000</featuredArtist>
        <album>Cole World: The Sideline Story</album>
        <trackNumber>17</trackNumber>
    </metadata>

<intro vocals="J_Cole" mood="ambiguous" tone="neutral">
<line>Who dat, who dat?</line>
<line>Who dat, who dat?</line>
<line>Who dat, who dat?</line>
</intro>

<verse vocals="J_Cole" mood="ambiguous" tone="neutral">
<line>Hey, who dat, who dat? That nigga you been waiting for</line>
<line>I mean the shit was all bad just a week ago</line>
<line>Rappers was bullshitting, fuck it I ain't hating though</line>
<topic type="religion"><line>Because now a nigga hot enough to fuck with one of Satan' hoes</line></topic>
<topic type="religion"><line>And she can't tell the difference, I been through hell conditions</line></topic>
<topic type="religion"><line>Wishing for air conditioning, feeling God was never listening</line></topic>
<line>Now I'm on television, and did I fail to mention?</line>
<line>Your bitch is tired of missionary, boy you failed the mission</line>
<line>Speaking of positions just witness how I elevate it</line>
<line>Real niggas celebrate it, finger fuck whoever hate it</line>
<line>My life accelerated, but had to wait my turn</line>
<line>Then I redecorated, that mean my tables turned</line>
<line>Live life, might as well, only way to learn</line>
<line>Is try and fail, clientele the only way to earn</line>
<topic type="drugs"><line>So if you're selling crack, or if you're selling rap</line></topic>
<line>Make sure it's mean so them fiends keep on coming back</line>
</verse>

<chorus vocals="J_Cole" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<line>Who dat, who dat? Bitch I got that flame</line>
<line>Who dat, who dat? Bitch I got that flame</line>
<line>Who dat, who dat? Bitch I got that flame</line>
<line>So don't worry about my motherfucking name</line>
<line>I got them saying who dat, who dat? Cole World</line>
<line>Who dat, who dat? I got them saying</line>
<line>Who dat, who dat? Cole World</line>
<line>Who dat, who dat?</line>
</chorus>
  
<verse vocals="J_Cole" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<line>Hey, the mind state of a winner</line>
<line>When you thinking about summertime I'm thinking about the winter</line>
<line>When you thinking about breakfast I'm heating up my dinner</line>
<line>I was plotting this moment back when y'all was riding spinners</line>
<topic type="religion"><line>Yeah I'm a menace, God as my witness, with this pen I'm insane, yup</line></topic>
<line>Hungry like the nigga who ain't got the taste of fame yet</line>
<line>Clown told me, “Ain't you Roc? But where the fuck your chain at?”</line>
<line>Guess it's something like your girl, nigga it ain't came yet</line>
<line>The man make the chain, chain don't make the man</line>
<topic type="wealth"><line>How many niggas do we know with hella ice but yet they lame?</line></topic>
<line>The cloth from which we came, me and them is not the same</line>
<line>It's like we all headed to Spain they took the boat I took the plane, damn</line>
<line>That boy's sick now hoes on his joystick</line>
<line>Heating up like May weather, dog I'm on that Floyd shit</line>
<line>Boy stick to your day job, said you was hot? Well, they lied</line>
<line>Is that your girl? Well, I just G'd her, no A-Rod</line>
</verse>

<chorus vocals="J_Cole" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<line>Who dat, who dat? Bitch I got that flame</line>
<line>Who dat, who dat? Bitch I got that flame</line>
<line>Who dat, who dat? Bitch I got that flame</line>
<line>So don't worry about my motherfucking name</line>
<line>I got them saying who dat, who dat? Cole World</line>
<line>Who dat, who dat? I got them saying</line>
<line>Who dat, who dat? Cole World</line>
<line>Who dat, who dat?</line>
</chorus>    
 
<verse vocals="Andre_3000" mood="null" tone="null">
<line>Now who else want to fuck with Hollywood Cole?</line>
</verse>

<verse vocals="J_Cole" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<line>The little engine that could, this little nigga is good</line>
<line>Rappers claiming they sick, I heal niggas for good</line>
<line>A couple of y'all ain't took a field trip to the hood</line>
<line>And me? I'm fresh prince, I'm Will Smith to the hood</line>
<line>Baby, ain't saying names but we not the same</line>
<topic type="money"><line>All the money and the fame don't change the fact that you lame</line></topic>
<line>Might want to grab you a chain, want to tip up your hat</line>
<line>Might want to purchase some game, homey your shit is so wack</line>
<line>I got my finger on the trigger, tell that nigga, “hold that”</line>
<line>Want picture perfect baby you can check the Kodak</line>
<line>Hey, so anything you can do I can do better</line>
<line>And any chick you can screw I can get wetter</line>
<line>I'm young, black, gifted, live my life on the run</line>
<line>Bet your bottom dollar before I'm done</line>
<line>They say that I'm the one, ya nigga I'm the one</line>
<line>I got them saying</line>
</verse>

<chorus vocals="J_Cole" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<line>Who dat, who dat? Bitch I got that flame</line>
<line>Who dat, who dat? Bitch I got that flame</line>
<line>Who dat, who dat? Bitch I got that flame</line>
<line>So don't worry about my motherfucking name</line>
<line>I got them saying who dat, who dat? Cole World</line>
<line>Who dat, who dat? I got them saying</line>
<line>Who dat, who dat? Cole World</line>
<line>Who dat, who dat?</line>
</chorus>
</song>