<?xml-model href="../../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <artist>J.Cole</artist>
        <year>2021</year>
        <title>Pride is the Devil</title>
        <featuredArtist>Lil Baby</featuredArtist>
        <album>The Off-Season</album>
        <trackNumber>7</trackNumber>
    </metadata>
<intro vocals="J_Cole" mood="ambiguous" tone="neutral">
<line>Uh</line>
</intro>

<chorus vocals="J_Cole" mood="anxious" tone="negative">
<line>Pride is the Devil</line>
<line>Think it got a hold on me</line>
<line>Pride is the Devil</line>
<topic type="death"><line>It left so many R.I.P. </line></topic>
<line>Pride is the Devil</line>
<line>Think it got a hold on me</line>
<line>Pride is the Devil, yeah, uh</line>
</chorus>

<chorus vocals="J_Cole" mood="anxious" tone="negative">
<line>Terrified, paranoid, I'll put you over everything to fill the void</line>
<line>And when you’re gone, will I have anything or will I be destroyed? Uh</line>
<line>Terrified, paranoid, I'll put you over everything to fill the void</line>
<line>And when you're gone, will I have anything or will I be destroyed? Yеah</line>
</chorus>

<verse vocals="J_Cole" mood="anxious" tone="negative">
<line>Bright lights pass me in the city, it’s emеrgency</line>
<topic type="violence"><line>I'm thankful 'cause I made it past my thirties, no one murdered me</line></topic>
<line>Still remember vividly the nigga that pulled a gun on me</line>
<line>I'm petrified, but moving like I got no sense of urgency</line>
<line>Pride make a nigga act way harder than he really be</line>
<line>Pride hide the shame when city cut off all utilities</line>
<topic type="poverty"><line>Pride hide the pain of growing up inhaling poverty</line></topic>
<line>Pride make a nigga feel a way that you unfollowed me</line>
<topic type="money"><line>Make a nigga flash a thousand like he hit the lottery</line></topic>
<line>Make a baby mama make shit harder than it gotta be</line>
<line>Make you have to take the bitch to court to see your prodigy</line>
<line>Make you have to use your last resort and pull a robbery</line>
<topic type="family"><line>Pride be the reason for the family dichotomy</line></topic>
<topic type="family"><line>Got uncles and some aunties that's too proud to give apologies</line></topic>
<line>Slowly realizing what the root of all my problems be</line>
<line>It got me feeling different when somebody say they proud of me</line>
</verse>

<chorus vocals="J_Cole" mood="anxious" tone="negative">
<line>Pride is the Devil, uh</line>
<line>I think it got a hold on me</line>
<line>Pride is the Devil, uh</line>
<topic type="death"><line>It left so many R.I.P. </line></topic>
<line>Pride is the Devil</line>
<line>I think it got a hold on me</line>
<line>Pride is the Devil, uh, yeah</line>
</chorus>
 
<chorus vocals="J_Cole" mood="anxious" tone="negative">
<line>Terrified, paranoid, I'll put you over everything to fill the void</line>
<line>And when you're gone, will I have anything or will I be destroyed? Uh</line>
<line>Terrified, paranoid, I'll put you over everything to fill the void</line>
<line>And when you’re gone, will I have anything or will I be destroyed? Yeah</line>
</chorus>

<bridge vocals="J_Cole" mood="anxious" tone="negative">
<topic type="money"><line>Too much money to count, what’s the amount?</line></topic>
<topic type="money"><line>Check never bounce</line></topic>
<topic type="money"><line>I gotta pay a nigga to add it up</line></topic>
<topic type="money"><line>Then pay somebody to make sure whatever amount he say he can back it up</line></topic>
<topic type="wealth"><line>Got racks on racks, I'm rackin’ up, stackin' up</line></topic>
<line>You're reachin', I’m actin' up</line>
</bridge>

<verse vocals="Lil_Baby" mood="null" tone="null">
<line>Break it down, weigh it up, now bag it up</line>
<topic type="money"><line>Making five a month, that's regular</line></topic>
<line>Nigga playing with us, that's a negative</line>
<line>Go back to start, that's never</line>
<line>I'm a boss, my closet leather</line>
<line>Ain't no off-days on my schedule</line>
<line>Long as I live, we live forever</line>
<line>Told my twin this shit get better</line>
<line>These niggas done slipped, let me ahead 'em</line>
<line>Got my feet up, I paid silly bands to have sex on the jet</line>
<line>I don't need 'em, that shit in the past, I'm feelin' like what's next</line>
<line>Got my speed up, foot all on the gas, this not a C8 'Vette</line>
<line>I can beat 'em, I believe in me, just tell me what's the bet</line>
<topic type="wealth"><line>All my pride gone, had to lose it all then I got rich</line></topic>
<topic type="wealth"><line>I own five homes, glad some of this shit starting to make sense</line></topic>
<line>I'm staying hella focused and I can't forget the bigger picture</line>
<line>I can't even hold you, I didn't have shit, I won't forget it</line>
<line>Will I be destroyed?</line>
<line>Come to me with everything, it's starting to get annoying</line>
<line>I'm addicted to promethazine, it's crazy, yeah, I know it</line>
<topic type="money"><line>All this money coming in, it drive me crazy not to show it</line></topic>
<line>I'll be crazy if I blow it</line>
</verse>

<chorus vocals="J_Cole" mood="anxious" tone="negative">
<line>Pride is the Devil, uh</line>
<line>I think it got a hold on me</line>
<line>Pride is the Devil, uh</line>
<topic type="death"><line>And it left so many R.I.P. </line></topic>
<line>Pride is the Devil</line>
<line>I think it got a hold on me</line>
<line>Pride is the Devil, uh</line>
</chorus>
</song>