<?xml-model href="../../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <artist>J.Cole</artist>
        <year>2021</year>
        <title>let.go.my.hand</title>
        <featuredArtist>Bas &amp; 6LACK</featuredArtist>
        <album>The Off-Season</album>
    </metadata>

<chorus vocals="J-Cole" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<line>Soldier's song, marching on, on</line>
<line>Hoping to see home</line>
<topic type="death"><line>If I die before I</line></topic>
<line>See your smile just one more time</line>
</chorus>

<verse vocals="J_Cole" mood="anxious" tone="negative">
<line>Sometimes I question whether this shit matters</line>
<line>Puttin' substance into something in a world so used to instant gratification</line>
<line>I found this instrumental on my phone while on vacation</line>
<line>Ib sent it a year ago or so</line>
<line>I probably heard it before, but slept on it, you know?</line>
<line>Shit don't always connect as soon as you press play</line>
<line>At times you gotta step away, do some livin'</line>
<line>Let time provide a new prescription, givin' truer vision</line>
<topic type="religion"><line>I dibble-dabble in a few religions</line></topic>
<topic type="religion"><line>My homie constantly telling me 'bout Quran, puttin' me on</line></topic>
<line>I read a few pages and recognize the wisdom in it</line>
<line>But I ain't got the discipline for stickin' with it</line>
<line>Now I'm on the way to London, got a show for seven digits</line>
<line>I'm wonderin' just when did I become my biggest critic?</line>
<line>I wanna be my biggest fan, like how I was when didn't nobody know my jams</line>
<topic type="family"><line>Today my son said, "Dad, let go my hand"</line></topic>
<line>Reminded me one day he's gonna be his own man</line>
<line>And my job is to make sure he's equipped</line>
<line>I gotta make sure he not no bitch 'cause niggas bound to try him</line>
<line>If I said I was the toughest growin' up, I would be lyin'</line>
<line>I had a fear of gettin' punched while everybody eyein'</line>
<line>Add to that a constant fear of dyin'</line>
<topic type="violence"><line>By gunshot wound, the other violent type of endings</line></topic>
<line>I kept a tough demeanor on the surface but was mostly just pretendin'</line>
<line>Luckily my bluff was workin' way more often than not</line>
<line>But sometimes a nigga pulled my card, tryna expose me for a fraud</line>
<line>And with my reputation at stake</line>
<line>I was scufflin' just to save face</line>
<line>Couple wins, couple losses, some broken up too quick to call it</line>
<line>My last scrap was with Puff Daddy, who would've thought it?</line>
<line>I bought that nigga album in seventh grade and played it so much</line>
<line>You would've thought my favorite rapper was Puff</line>
<line>Back then I ain't know shit, now I know too much</line>
<line>Ignorance is bliss and innocence is just ignorance before it's introduced to currency and clips</line>
<line>Or bad licks that have a nigga servin' three to six, shit</line>
</verse>

<chorus vocals="J_Cole Bas 6LACK" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<line>Soldier's song, marching on, on</line>
<line>Hoping to see home</line>
<topic type="death"><line>If I die before I</line></topic>
<line>See your smile just one more time</line>
</chorus>

<bridge vocals="Bas" mood="null" tone="null">
<line>Soldier's song</line>
<line>I could be one to lean on</line>
<line>Time will right the wrongs</line>
<line>Won't be long</line>
<line>How can we grow any closer?</line>
<line>How can we grow any closer?</line>
<line>How can we grow any closer?</line>
<line>How can we grow any closer?</line>
<line>Something inside of me's tryna crawl up to the surface</line>
<line>Something is suddenly smothering, stopping me</line>
<line>Stubbornly getting its way <background>Way</background>, way <background>Way</background></line>
<line>Drowning out the wave <background>Drowning out</background></line>
<line>I've got a reason to believe that I'll turn out just fine</line>
<line>Soldier's song</line>
</bridge>

<outro vocals="Diddy" mood="null" tone="null">
<topic type="religion"><line>Lord, please guide our steps</line></topic>
<line>Watch us, cover us</line>
<line>So that every move we make is in alignment with Your will</line>
<line>Your purpose</line>
<line>Please fill us with Your spirit</line>
<line>Keep us forever in the present</line>
<line>For presence makes the strongest fathers</line>
<line>Teach us how to lead</line>
<line>Show us how to love</line>
</outro>
</song>