<?xml-model href="../../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <artist>J.Cole</artist>
        <year>2009</year>
        <title>Lights Please</title>
        <featuredArtist>None</featuredArtist>
        <album>The Warm Up</album>
    </metadata>
    
<verse vocals="J_Cole" mood="ambiguous" tone="neutral">
<line>Yeah, I had this little bad thing, somethin' like them tens</line>
<line>She gave a nigga mad brain, somethin' like The Wiz</line>
<line>But, you see, the sad thing fuckin' with her is</line>
<line>Is the chick ain't even have brains, dummy like a bitch</line>
<line>So I tried to show her about the world</line>
<line>And about just who we really are</line>
<line>And where we've come and how we still have to go really far</line>
<topic type="poverty"><line>Like, "Baby, look at how we live broke on the boulevard"</line></topic>
<line>But all she ever want me to do is unhook her bra</line>
<line>Then all I really want is for her to go down low</line>
<line>Before you know it, she wet enough to get drowned slow</line>
<line>And all that deep shit I was previously down fo'</line>
<line>Replaced by freak shit I am currently down fo'</line>
<line>You see I peeped it, pussy is power</line>
<line>That proud feelin' we get knowin' that pussy is ours</line>
<line>And how it feels to feel that feelin'</line>
<line>You feelin' when you be drillin' that shit</line>
<line>Got her sayin' you be killin' that shit</line>
<line>And all the pain the world cause, she be healin' that shit</line>
<line>And naw, that ain't your girl, dog</line>
<line>But you be feelin' that chick</line>
<line>And you just wanna tell her everything she might need</line>
<line>But in the meantime it's lights, please</line>
</verse>

<chorus vocals="J_Cole" mood="hopeful" tone="positive">
<line>Lights please, lights please, turn off the lights</line>
<line>For now, everything just seems so right</line>
<line>And how you make the darkness seem so bright</line>
<line>I'm feeling like things gon' be alright</line>
<line>Lights please, lights please, turn off the lights</line>
<line>For now, everything just seems so right</line>
<line>And how you make the darkness seem so bright</line>
<line>I'm feeling like things gon' be alright</line>
</chorus>

<verse vocals="J_Cole" mood="anxious" tone="negative">
<line>So now we in the hotel, mirrors on the ceilin'</line>
<line>She say she wanna blow L's, I hear her and I'm willin'</line>
<topic type="drugs"><line>But every time I smoke, well, a nigga mind gone</line></topic>
<line>So that every word I spoke, well, I'm tryna put her on</line>
<line>But she couldn't hear me</line>
<line>I told her all about how we been livin' a lie</line>
<topic type="death"><line>And that they love to see us all go to prison or die</line></topic>
<topic type="social_issues"><line> Like, "Baby, look at how they show us on the TV screen"</line></topic>
<line>But all she ever want me to do is unzip her jeans</line>
<line>Then all I really want is for her to get on top</line>
<line>Before you know it, she workin', jerkin' it nonstop</line>
<line>And all that next shit I was previously talkin'</line>
<line>Is now that wet shit that I'm currently lost in</line>
<line>And while that sweat drip, I am reminded</line>
<line>All the times my brother told me that pussy is blindin'</line>
<line>I'm findin', the more I grow</line>
<line>The more y'all seem to stay the same</line>
<line>Don't even know the rules, but yet y'all tryna play the game</line>
<line>And ain't it shameful how niggas blame hoes for givin' birth</line>
<line>To a baby that took two to make?</line>
<line>Coward nigga, you a fake</line>
<line>How you gonna look in your son's face and turn your back</line>
<topic type="family"><line>Then go start another family?</line></topic>
<line>Dawg, what type of shit is that?</line>
<line>She said it's okay, rub my head and told me to relax</line>
<line>Laid a nigga down proper, like she was recordin' tracks</line>
<line>Said "I know you wanna change the world</line>
<line>But for the night, please</line>
<line>Just reach over and hit the lights please"</line>
</verse>
   
<chorus vocals="J_Cole" mood="hopeful" tone="positive">
<line>Lights please, lights please, turn off the lights</line>
<line>For now, everything just seems so right</line>
<line>And how you make the darkness seem so bright</line>
<line>I'm feeling like things gon' be alright</line>
<line>Lights please, lights please, turn off the lights</line>
<line>For now, everything just seems so right</line>
<line>And how you make the darkness seem so bright</line>
<line>I'm feeling like things gon' be alright</line>
<line>Lights please, ah-ah-ah</line>
<line>Lights please, ah-ah-ah</line>
<line>Lights please, ah-ah-ah</line>
<line>Lights please, turn off the lights</line>
<line>Lights, please</line>
</chorus>

<outro vocals="J_Cole" mood="determined" tone="neutral">
<line>Alright, if y'all niggas heard the first one, The Come Up and shit, </line>
<line>then you would have heard part 1 of this joint right here. It's </line>
<topic type="money"><line>"Dead Presidents", you know classic nigga, that's classic Jay shit. </line></topic>
<line>So I did it, threw it on the first mixtape, this is about a year ago. </line>
<line>We let niggas hear like you know the mixtape whatever, and </line>
<line>there was always this one nigga that stuck out to me like a year ago. This nigga's like "yo". like I thought I did my thing on this </line>
<line>shit, that was like two of my favorite verses that I did, but he was </line>
<line>just like "Yo", like, "Yo you didn't come right man. If you gon' </line>
<topic type="money"><line>come on Dead Presidents son, you gotta come, hard son, </line></topic>
<line>you gotta come harder than that son, you gotta come harder than that." </line>
<line>I was like, man what you mean I came hard? But, that shit </line>
<line>always stuck in my mind, so doing this next, you know, doing this </line>
<line>The Warm Up I was like, damn, I gotta get on it again, I gotta do </line>
<line>it again. Just almost like, just to prove to that nigga and kinda </line>
<line>prove to myself that you I can, I can maybe get a little...</line>
</outro>
</song>