<?xml-model href="../../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <artist>J.Cole</artist>
        <year>2011</year>
        <title>Lost Ones</title>
        <featuredArtist>None</featuredArtist>
        <album>Cole World: The Sideline Story</album>
    </metadata>
 
<intro vocals="J_Cole" mood="ambiguous" tone="neutral">
<line>Uh-uh, uh-uh</line>
<line>One, two, one, two, one, two, one, two, yeah</line>
<line>Uh-uh, uh-uh</line>
<line>One, two, one, two, one, two, one, two, yeah</line>
<line>Uh</line>
</intro>

<verse vocals="J_Cole" mood="angry" tone="negative">
<line>Baby girl, I can't imagine what it's like for you</line>
<topic type="social_issues"><line>I got you pregnant, now inside there is a life in you</line></topic>
<line>I know you wonderin' if this is gon' make me think 'bout wifin' you</line>
<line>Like, if you have my first child</line>
<line>Would I spend my whole life with you?</line>
<line>Now, I ain't tryna pick a fight with you, I'm tryna talk</line>
<line>Now, I ain't tryna spend the night with you, I'm kinda lost</line>
<line>See, I've been givin' it some thought lately</line>
<line>And frankly I feel like we ain't ready and this—</line>
<line>Hold up now, let me finish!</line>
<line>Think about it, baby, me and you, we still kids ourself</line>
<line>How we gonna raise a kid by ourself?</line>
<line>Handle biz by ourself? A nigga barely over twenty</line>
<topic type="poverty"><line>Where the hell we gon' live? Where am I gon' get that money?</line></topic>
<line>I refuse to bring my boy or my girl in this world</line>
<line>When I ain't got shit to give 'em, and I'm not with them niggas</line>
<line>Who be knockin' girls up and skate out</line>
<line>So, girl, you gotta think about how the options weigh out</line>
<line>What's the way out?</line>
<line>Uh</line>
</verse>

<verse vocals="J_Cole" mood="sad" tone="negative">
<line>And I ain't too proud to tell you</line>
<line>That I cry sometime, I cry sometimes about it</line>
<line>And girl, I know it hurt, but if this world was perfect</line>
<line>Then we could make it work, but I doubt it</line>
<line>And I ain't too proud to tell you</line>
<line>That I cry sometime, I cry sometimes about it</line>
<line>And girl, I know it hurt, but if this world was perfect</line>
<line>Then we could make it work, but I doubt it</line>
</verse>

<verse vocals="J_Cole" mood="angry" tone="negative">
<line>She said: "Nigga, you got some nerve</line>
<line>To come up to me talkin' about abortion</line>
<topic type="social_issues"><line>This my body, nigga, so don't think you finna force shit!</line></topic>
<line>See, I knew that this is how you act, so typical</line>
<line>Said you love me, oh, but now you flippin' like reciprocals</line>
<line>It figures though, I should've known</line>
<line>That you was just another nigga</line>
<line>No different from them other niggas</line>
<line>Who be claimin' that they love you just to get up in them drawers</line>
<line>Knowin' all the right things to say</line>
<line>I let you hit it raw, mothafucka!</line>
<line>Now I'm pregnant, you don't wanna get involved, mothafucka?</line>
<line>Tryna take away a life—is you God, mothafucka?!</line>
<line>I don't think so! This a new life up in my stomach</line>
<line>Regardless if I'm your wife, this new life here, I'ma love it</line>
<line>I ain't budgin', I just do this by my mothafuckin' self</line>
<topic type="family"><line>See, my mama raised me without no mothafuckin' help</line></topic>
<line>From a man, but I still don't understand how you could say that</line>
<line>Did you forget all those conversations that we had way back</line>
<topic type="family"><line>'Bout your father? And you told me that you hate that nigga</line></topic>
<line>Talkin' about he a coward and you so glad that you ain't that nigga</line>
<topic type="social_issues"><line>‘Cause he left your mama when she had you and he ain't shit</line></topic>
<line>And here you go doin' the same shit… You ain't shit, nigga!"</line>
</verse>

<verse vocals="J_Cole" mood="sad" tone="negative">
<line>And I ain't too proud to tell you</line>
<line>That I cry sometimes, I cry sometimes about it</line>
<line>And boy, this shit hurts, and ain’t nobody perfect</line>
<line>Still we can make it work, but you doubt it</line>
<line>And I ain't too proud to tell you</line>
<line>That I cry sometimes, I cry sometimes about it</line>
<line>And boy, this shit hurts, and ain’t nobody perfect</line>
<line>Still we can make it work, but you doubt it</line>
</verse>

<verse vocals="J_Cole" mood="anxious" tone="negative">
<line>They say everything happens for a reason</line>
<line>And people change like the seasons, then grow apart</line>
<line>She wanted him to show his heart and say he loved her</line>
<line>He spoke the magic words and on the same day he fucked her</line>
<line>Now she wide open</line>
<line>She'd put a ring up on his finger if she could</line>
<line>But he loved her ‘cause the pussy good</line>
<line>But she ain't no wife though</line>
<line>Uh-oh! She tellin' him she missed her period, like typos</line>
<line>He panickin', froze up like a mannequin, a life grows</line>
<line>Inside her, and now he askin': "Is it even mine?"</line>
<line>What if this bitch ain't even pregnant? Dog, could she be lyin'?</line>
<line>And she be cryin', ‘cause he actin' distant</line>
<line>Like, "Ever since I told you this, nigga, you actin' different."</line>
<line>And all his niggas sayin', "Man, these hoes be trappin' niggas</line>
<line>Playin' with niggas' emotions like they some action figures."</line>
<line>Swear they get pregnant for collateral, it's like extortion</line>
<line>Man, if that bitch really pregnant, tell her to get a abortion <background>Uh</background></line>
<line>But what about your seed, nigga? <background>Uh-uh</background></line>
<line>But what about your seed, nigga?</line>
<line>But what about your seed, nigga?</line>
<line>But what about your seed, nigga?</line>
    </verse>
    
<outro vocals="J_Cole" mood="sad" tone="negative">
<line>And I ain't too proud to tell you</line>
<line>That I cry sometime, I cry sometimes about it</line>
<line>And I ain't too proud to tell you</line>
<line>That I cry sometime, I cry sometimes about it</line>
</outro>
</song>