<?xml-model href="../../../../hip-hop-humanities/relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <artist>Vince Staples</artist>
        <year>2021</year>
        <title>Take Me Home</title>
        <featuredArtist>Fousheé</featuredArtist>
        <album>Vince Staples</album>
        <trackNumber>7</trackNumber>
    </metadata>
    <intro vocals="Fousheé" mood="null" tone="null">
        <line>(One, two, three, four) Yeah</line>
        <line>Yeah</line>
        <line>Yeah, yeah</line>
        <line>Three, four, one, two</line>
    </intro>
    <verse vocals="Vince Staples" mood="anxious" tone="negative">
        <line>I don't wanna die, but I will for the cause (Dead homies)</line>
        <line>Swallowing my pride like them pills y'all be off (Hell nah, yeah)</line>
        <topic type="drugs"><line>I hate when you high, but you hate feeling lost (Where we at with it?)</line></topic>
        <line>I hate every time that you ask, "Can we talk?" (Hell nah, yeah)</line>
        <line>Tell me what I did now, drying off your tears now</line>
        <line>Fighting for some years now, something gotta give (For real)</line>
        <line>I don't wanna rebound, I just wanna sleep sound</line>
        <line>Don't wanna dream 'bout the shit I done did (Walk 'em down)</line>
        <line>You know these trips come with baggage (Yeah), been all 'cross this atlas</line>
        <line>But keep coming back to this place 'cause they trapped us (The hood)</line>
        <line>I preach what I practice, these streets all I know</line>
        <line>And there's no place like home (No place like home, six-eight, yeah)</line>
    </verse>
    <chorus vocals="Fousheé" mood="ambiguous" tone="negative">
        <line>Ooh (Alright, alright)</line>
        <line>Take, take me home, like I clicked my shoes (Aw yeah, aw yeah)</line>
        <line>I'm up, the price is sky-high (Sky-high)</line>
        <line>Please save your two cents, I'm fine</line>
        <line>I got no sensor, I vibe</line>
        <line>Like, "Ooh, ah, ooh, ah"</line>
        <line>Only abide by my rules</line>
    </chorus>
    <verse vocals="Vince Staples" mood="apathetic" tone="negative">
        <line>Yeah, I'm on PCH, going south, blower on the seat</line>
        <line>With the windows down, music loud, let 'em hear the beat (Let 'em hear it now)</line>
        <line>When it's quiet out, I hear the sound of those who rest in peace</line>
        <topic type="violence"><line>Tryna drown the violence out (Dead homies), but let 'em say that they want beef</line></topic>
        <line>And we riding out, finding out where them niggas be (Where they be at with it?)</line>
        <line>If they hanging out, lay 'em out, airing out the street (Knock 'em down)</line>
        <line>Then it's out the way, out-of-state, please don't tell on me (PCH)</line>
        <line>Don't need no more felonies (Please), all these broken memories (Please)</line>
        <line>I be solo dolo, never know who working with police (Yeah)</line>
        <line>When I hit the set, it's loaded; I don't know who envy me</line>
        <line>I'm the only one who made it out—you remember me?</line>
        <line>Is you a frenemy? You plan on killing me? No?</line>
    </verse>
    <chorus vocals="Fousheé" mood="apathetic" tone="neutral">
        <line>Ooh (Alright, alright)</line>
        <line>Take, take me home like I clicked my shoes (Aw yeah, aw yeah)</line>
        <line>I'm up, the price is sky-high (Sky-high)</line>
        <line>Please save your two cents, I'm fine</line>
        <line>I got no sensor, I vibe</line>
        <line>Like, "Ooh, ah, ooh, ah"</line>
        <line>Only abide by my rules</line>
    </chorus>
    <outro vocals="Fousheé" mood="ambiguous" tone="negative">
        <line>Ooh (Yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah)</line>
        <line>And I make mistakes sometimes</line>
        <line>I</line>
        <line>I tried</line>
        <line>I can't tell you who's an ally</line>
        <line>I can't tell you who</line>
        <line>Who</line>
    </outro>
</song>
