<?xml-model href="relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <artist>Vince Staples</artist>
        <year>2021</year>
        <title>Taking Trips</title>
        <album>Vince Staples</album>
    </metadata>
    <intro vocals="Vince Staples" mood="ambiguous" tone="neutral">
        <line>Yeah, ugh, ugh</line>
        <line>Trippin' (Yeah), trippin' (Ugh, trippin')</line>
        <line>Trippin' (Trippin', huh, yeah), trippin' (Yeah)</line>
        <line>Yeah</line>
    </intro>
    <verse vocals="Vince Staples" mood="ambiguous" tone="neutral">
        <line>Listen (Listen), I ain't going (Nah), riding foreign</line>
        <line>Riches off of tourin' (Yeah), call-ignoring</line>
        <line>Missions, miss my brothers (Yeah), die for colors (Miss my, miss my)</line>
        <line>Quidditch, catching snitches (Snitch), do him vicious</line>
        <line>Living, like Khadijah, quick to leave her (I ain't never really know the bitch,
            man)</line>
        <line>Just because, like Anita (Baker), she in love</line>
        <line>But it's leisure (Nah, no), real around-the-corner bleeder (Yeah, Norfside)</line>
        <line>Bounce out on 'em on Artesia, now we got amnesia (Yeah, likе, "Where you from,
            cuz?")</line>
    </verse>
    <chorus vocals="Vince Staples" mood="ambiguous" tone="neutral">
        <line>Trippin', yeah (Yеah)</line>
        <line>Trippin', yeah (Trippin')</line>
        <line>Trippin' (Trippin', huh, yeah)</line>
        <line>Trippin', yeah (Yeah, yeah)</line>
        <line>Trippin', yeah (Yeah)</line>
        <line>Trippin', yeah (Ayy, who trippin'?)</line>
        <line>Trippin' (Yeah), yeah (Trippin')</line>
        <line>Trippin', yeah</line>
    </chorus>
    <verse vocals="Vince Staples" mood="angry" tone="negative">
        <line>I ain't gon' lie (Nah), always been the one to cuff (Uh-huh)</line>
        <line>I ain't gon' lie (Uh-huh), sometimes, I hit it once and then I'm stuck (Aw,
            yeah)</line>
        <line>I ain't gon' lie (Nah), no, you not the only one (You're never the only one,
            baby)</line>
        <line>I ain't gon' lie, she only want me 'cause I money-touch</line>
        <line>I hate July (I hate it, sheesh), crime is high, the summer sucks (We run it up)</line>
        <line>Can't even hit the beach without my heat, it's in my trunks</line>
        <line>They ride the tide (Yeah), I don't got no one to trust (Can't trust, you know what's
            out here, man)</line>
        <line>Trust and believe I see the shit that's up your sleeve (Ain't fooling nobody,
            cuz)</line>
        <line>Come fuck with me, we living fast as SRTs, yeah (Hundred on the dash)</line>
        <line>Don't come for me unless GoFundMe what you seek, yeah (Put you on your ass, lil'
            nigga)</line>
        <line>They lighting candles on the curb, they not Diptyques (Naw)</line>
        <line>My hood impatient (Yeah), so be wary if it's beef, yeah (Naw, you know how Norfside
            with it)</line>
        <line>Pull up, location is the belly of the beast, yeah (Ayy, pull up)</line>
        <topic type="violence"><line>This shit get deadly, hope you ready to decease, yeah (Ayy, rest in peace, nigga, you
            really not ready for this shit, man)</line></topic>
        <line>It's just you and me (You know it, you and me)</line>
        <line>Pay me what you owe, this shit ain't free</line>
        <line>Nah</line>
    </verse>
    <verse vocals="Vince Staples" mood="anxious" tone="negative">
        <topic type="gangs"><line>I knew very well that I was supposed to go straight home from school. I just couldn't
            refuse. I knew I was doing the wrong thing. But I guess it was more important to be
            accepted by the guys than anything else (Don't lie)</line></topic>
    </verse>
    <chorus vocals="Vince Staples" mood="ambiguous" tone="neutral">
        <line>Trippin', yeah (Yeah)</line>
        <line>Trippin', yeah (Trippin')</line>
        <line>Trippin' (Trippin', huh, yeah)</line>
        <line>Trippin', yeah (Yeah, yeah)</line>
        <line>Trippin', yeah (Yeah)</line>
        <line>Trippin', yeah (Ayy, who trippin'?)</line>
        <line>Trippin' (Yeah), yeah (Trippin')</line>
        <line>Trippin', yeah</line>
    </chorus>
    <outro vocals="Vince Staples" mood="cynical" tone="neutral">
        <topic type="gangs"><line>I mean, the fellas in the gang weren't the greatest. But I didn't wanna be left
            out</line></topic>
    </outro>
</song>
