<?xml-model href="../../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <artist>Kendrick Lamar</artist>
        <year>2010</year>
        <title>I Do This (Remix)</title>
        <featuredArtist>Y-O, Thurz, Skeme, Brown</featuredArtist>
        <album>Overly Dedicated</album>
        <trackNumber>16</trackNumber>
    </metadata>
    
<chorus vocals="Kendrick_Lamar" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<line>The homies say I'm the truest</line>
<line>The bitches think I'm the cutest</line>
<line>The definition what cool is</line>
<line>Boy, I thought you knew this</line>
<line>Bitch, I do this</line>
</chorus>

<verse vocals="Y_O" mood="null" tone="null">
<line>Now I prefer women with some sexy toes</line>
<line>With no corns but enjoys eating vegetables</line>
<line>Seem like everybody love the role of assholes</line>
<line>But I'm feeling better being crowned with some bad hoes</line>
<line>Mr. Michael of Amish yo speaking</line>
<line>Fedora on the top, the black Abraham Lincoln</line>
<line>I hear they fell in love with my penis</line>
<line>Only concerned with my balls like Venus</line>
</verse>

<verse vocals="Thurz" mood="null" tone="null">
<line>Huh, they say I'm rolling like a big shot</line>
<line>Kama Sutra missionary, fuck shit up on top</line>
<line>Say, I'm big time, Flavor Flav on a wristwatch</line>
<line>And all these chickens want that rooster, call it Big Cock</line>
<line>Co-co-co-cock that, aim and shoot that sure shot</line>
<line>U-N-I, T.D.E. be doing it so go head and hop</line>
<line>On that bandwagon of my genitals, not new to me</line>
<line>I’m still serving, broads on my TIP for gratuities</line>
</verse>
    
<chorus vocals="Kendrick_Lamar" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<line>The homies say I'm the truest</line>
<line>The bitches think I'm the cutest</line>
<line>The definition what cool is</line>
<line>Boy, I thought you knew this</line>
<line>Bitch, I do this</line>
<line>Bitch, I do this</line>
<line>Bitch, I do this</line>
<line>The definition what cool is</line>
<line>Boy, I thought you knew this</line>
<line>Bitch, I do this</line>
</chorus>

<verse vocals="Skeme" mood="null" tone="null">
<line>Oh Lord, here he come, there they go again</line>
<line>Kendrick got my cover fire, bitch I'm going in</line>
<line>Burn a swisher up, then I roll again</line>
<topic type="money"><line>Ee-Jay and Weezy, just make sure that dough keep rolling in, hah!</line></topic>
<line>Got the world going crazy</line>
<line>Big chrome .380 if a nigga try and play me</line>
<line>Nigga's swag wavy, chauffeur got me car-pooling</line>
<line>So when it come to stunting, bitch I do it</line>
</verse>

<verse vocals="Brown" mood="null" tone="null">
<line>Never been like you or wanted to be, I do me</line>
<line>She found out that I'm in a group, now she's a groupie</line>
<line>Don't need a watch that's full of diamonds to know that it's perfect timing</line>
<topic type="wealth"><line>We be shining blue and brown and got that golden Gucci</line></topic>
<line>Yeah, keep it simple stupid, all I see is trendy all around me</line>
<line>T.D.E. the movement, we Sore Losers out of Dallas County</line>
<line>Country accent, city fashion, lights are flashing on the cameras</line>
<line>Hoes are choosing, niggas' hating, we ain’t tripping, keep our balance</line>
</verse>
 
<chorus vocals="Kendrick_Lamar" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<line>The homies say I'm the truest</line>
<line>The bitches think I'm the cutest</line>
<line>The definition what cool is</line>
<line>Boy, I thought you knew this</line>
<line>Bitch, I do this</line>
<line>Bitch, I do this</line>
<line>Bitch, I do this</line>
<line>The definition what cool is</line>
<line>Boy, I thought you knew this</line>
<line>Bitch, I do this</line>
</chorus>

<verse vocals="Kendrick_Lamar" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<line>These hoes want to love me, man</line>
<line>So I'm like, what up? Uh what up?</line>
<line>Uh, bitch I do this remix stupid, fire burning, people looting</line>
<topic type="violence"><line>That's the chaos, comes from K. Dot swinging swords and hanging nooses</line></topic>
<line>Chucking deuces, then drop one, dropping music and I won</line>
<line>Call me hot or call me Pac, every eye on me and it's obviously</line>
<line>I'm close as next to kingdom come, I just run my city dude</line>
<line>You just make your city run, they hate to be next to you</line>
<line>Tables turn, say you earn rights to be the God MC</line>
<line>I'm 'bout to make that halo burn, now goddamn that's some irony</line>
<topic type="religion"><line>I am the messiah of society</line></topic>
<line>Beside a Halle Berry, feed me berries in Paris, oui-oui</line>
<line>I carry on a great endeavor, ambition leave all men grief</line>
<line>Like beliefs of Mason Betha, reporting from C-P-T motherfucker</line>
</verse>

<outro vocals="Kendrick_Lamar" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<line>Bitch, I do this</line>
<line>Bitch, I do this</line>
<line>The definition what cool is</line>
<line>Boy, I thought you knew this</line>
<line>Bitch, I do this</line>
</outro>
</song>