<?xml-model href="../../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <artist>Kendrick Lamar</artist>
        <year>2017</year>
        <title>ELEMENT</title>
        <featuredArtist>Kid Capri</featuredArtist>
        <album>DAMN</album>
        <trackNumber>4</trackNumber>
    </metadata>
    
<intro vocals="Kendrick_Lamar Kid_Capri" mood="ambiguous" tone="neutral">
<line>New Kung Fu Kenny</line>
<line>Ain't nobody prayin' for me</line>
<line>Y'all know, what happens on Earth stays on Earth</line>
<line>Here we go!</line>
<line>I don't give a fuck, I don't give a fuck</line>
<line>I don't give a, I don't give a, I don't give a fuck</line>
</intro>

<verse vocals="Kendrick_Lamar" mood="determined" tone="negative">
<topic type="death"><line>I'm willin' to die for this shit</line></topic>
<line>I done cried for this shit, might take a life for this shit</line>
<topic type="religion"><line>Put the Bible down and go eye for an eye for this shit</line></topic>
<line>D-O-T my enemy, won't catch a vibe for this shit, ayy</line>
<topic type="family"><line>I been stomped out in front of my mama</line></topic>
<topic type="family"><line>My daddy commissary made it to commas</line></topic>
<line>Bitch, all my grandmas dead</line>
<line>So ain't nobody prayin' for me, I'm on your head, ayy</line>
<line>Thirty millions later, know the feds watchin'</line>
<line>Auntie on my Telegram like, "Be cautious!"</line>
<line>I be hangin' out at Tam's, I be on Stockton</line>
<line>I don't do it for the 'Gram, I do it for Compton</line>
<line>I'm willin' to die for this shit, nigga</line>
<line>I'll take your fuckin' life for this shit, nigga</line>
<line>We ain't goin' back to broke, family sellin' dope</line>
<line>That's why you maney-ass rap niggas better know</line>
</verse>
    
<chorus vocals="Kendrick_Lamar" mood="confident" tone="neutral">
<line>If I gotta slap a pussy-ass nigga, I'ma make it look sexy</line>
<line>If I gotta go hard on a bitch, I'ma make it look sexy</line>
<line>I pull up, hop out, air out, made it look sexy</line>
<line>They won't take me out my element</line>
<line>Nah, take me out my element</line>
</chorus>

<verse vocals="Kendrick_Lamar" mood="ambiguous" tone="negative">
<line>I'm allergic to a bitch nigga, ayy</line>
<line>An imaginary rich nigga, ayy</line>
<topic type="wealth"><line>Seven figures ho, that's slimmer than my bitch figure, ayy</line></topic>
<line>Goin' digital and physical on all y'all, ayy</line>
<line>Bunch of criminals and money in my phone calls, ayy</line>
<line>We okay, we let the A1 fly</line>
<line>Relocate, jump on the same G5</line>
<line>Checkin' for me heavy 'cause I go, yeah, I go, yeah</line>
<line>They never been ready, yeah, I know, yeah, know, yeah</line>
<topic type="money"><line>100K spread across the floor, 'cross the floor, yeah</line></topic>
<line>None of y'all fuckin' with the flow, yeah, the flow, yeah</line>
<line>Years in the makin', and don't y'all mistake it</line>
<line>I got 'em by a landslide, we talkin' about races</line>
<line>You know this'll never be a tie, just look at they laces</line>
<line>You know careers take off, just gotta be patient</line>
<line>Mr. One through Five, that's the only logic</line>
<topic type="death"><line>Fake my death, go to Cuba, that's the only option</line></topic>
</verse>
    
<chorus vocals="Kendrick_Lamar" mood="confident" tone="neutral">
<line>If I gotta slap a pussy-ass nigga, I'ma make it look sexy</line>
<line>If I gotta go hard on a bitch, I'ma make it look sexy</line>
<line>I pull up, hop out, air out, made it look sexy</line>
<line>They won't take me out my element</line>
<line>Nah, take me out my element</line>
</chorus>

<bridge vocals="Kendrick_Lamar" mood="angry" tone="negative">
<line>Damned if I do, if I don't <background>Yuh</background></line>
<line>Goddamn us all if you won't <background>Yuh</background></line>
<line>Damn, damn, damn, it's a goddamn shame</line>
<line>You ain't front in line, get out the goddamn way</line>
</bridge>

<verse vocals="Kendrick_Lamar" mood="angry" tone="negative">
<line>Niggas thought they wasn't gonna see me, huh?</line>
<line>Niggas thought that K-Dot real life</line>
<line>Was the same life they see on TV, huh?</line>
<line>Niggas wanna flex on me and be in L.A. for free, huh?</line>
<line>Next time they hit the 10 freeway, we need a receipt, huh?</line>
<line>'Cause most of y'all ain't real, most of y'all gon' squeal</line>
<line>Most of y'all just envy, but jealousy get you killed</line>
<line>Most of y'all throw rocks and try to hide your hand</line>
<line>Just say his name and I promise that you'll see Candyman</line>
<line>Because it's all in your eyes, most of y'all tell lies</line>
<line>Most of y'all don't fade, most of y'all been advised</line>
<line>Last LP I tried to lift the black artists</line>
<line>But it's a difference 'tween black artists and wack artists</line>
</verse>

<chorus vocals="Kendrick_Lamar Kid_Capri" mood="confident" tone="neutral">
<line>If I gotta slap a pussy-ass nigga, I'ma make it look sexy</line>
<line>It's the one and only, the world's greatest, the Kid Capri</line>
<line>If I gotta go hard on a bitch, I'ma make it look sexy</line>
<line>I pull up, hop out, air out, made it look sexy</line>
<line>They won't take me out my element</line>
<line>Nah, take me out my element</line>
</chorus>
</song>