<?xml-model href="../../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <artist>Kendrick Lamar</artist>
        <year></year>
        <title></title>
        <featuredArtist>Dash Snow, Daniel Joseph, Alori Joh</featuredArtist>
        <album></album>
    </metadata>
    
<intro vocals="Dash_Snow Daniel_Joseph Kendrick_Lamar" mood="cynical" tone="negative">
<line>"I’ll tell you what I don’t believe in, can I do that? All right, I don’t believe in laws, or the system by any means, whatsoever. I try not to obey them at anytime. That's what I believe in not believing in."</line>
<line>"So what keeps you alive?"</line>
<topic type="death"><line>"Four big bottles of water a day, two packs of Marlboro Reds. And, uh, I don’t - what keeps me alive, shit. Music, I have to listen to music all day long. I'd say that keeps me going. I’m a pretty dark person, I’ve thought about ending it a million times. And I have to say that music keeps me here, by far, the main thing."</line></topic>
<line>Thank you</line>
</intro>
    
<verse vocals="Kendrick_Lamar" mood="sad" tone="negative">
<line>Sitting in the studio thinking about which mood would go</line>
<line>Right now, freestyle or write down, whatever</line>
<line>It still'll come up clever, I just need to free my thoughts</line>
<line>And Lord knows that I know better, but I ain't perfect</line>
<topic type="religion"><line>I ain't seen too many churches or know them testament verses</line></topic>
<line>You should either hear me now or go deaf</line>
<topic type="death"><line>Or end up dead, die trying and know death</line></topic>
<topic type="death"><line>Might end up dead, swallow blood, swallow my breath</line></topic>
<line>Fuck a funeral, just make sure you pay my music respect, nigga</line>
<line>I mean that from the bottom of my heart</line>
<line>You see my art is all I have</line>
<line>And victory tastes sweet, even when the enemy can throw salt</line>
<line>Still knock them out the park like a fucking tow car</line>
<line>Let bygones be bygones, but where I'm from</line>
<line>We buy guns and more guns to give to the young</line>
<line>I'm living the life of a nigga trapped, nigga</line>
<line>Inside the system all you envision is trap niggas</line>
<line>My uncle doing life inside prison; he wasn't wrapped too tight</line>
<line>He told me "Rap about life, not rap niggas"</line>
<line>That's why I'm shaking my head when you rap-dissin'</line>
<line>My stomach start turning, my nerves get to twitching</line>
<line>I start evaluating, then my final intuition</line>
<line>Is that you wishing a come up, would just come up</line>
<line>We used to beefing over turf, fuck beefing over a verse</line>
<line>Niggas dying, motherfuck a double entendre</line>
<line>And this is Comp-ton, lions in the land of the triumph</line>
<line>Wrap-Saran our defiance, ban our alliance</line>
<line>Put burners in the hands of the black man</line>
<line>One hood with 20 four-fours like a cloned Kobe Bryant</line>
<line>You probably heard I wanna be heard and wonder who I am</line>
<topic type="religion"><line>You probably even listened to "Faith," and think I know Zion</line></topic>
<line>But really I'm just caught in the loop, of understanding the truth</line>
<line>Because it seem like it's always clashing with science</line>
<line>I got a big fear of flying</line>
<line>My future so bright I'd probably go blind before I blink twice</line>
<line>I ain't lying</line>
<line>I swear to God, half of y'all just don't know Kendrick</line>
<line>The school of hard knocks, we was the first ones in attendance</line>
<topic type="violence"><line>You walking down the block, he got shot, you are no eye witness</line></topic>
<line>You just mind your business</line>
<line>You just turn your head, kneel down and then tie your tennis</line>
<line>It's kind of scary, ain't it?</line>
<line>You can't act like no bitch, that only got Tyler Perry famous</line>
<line>Just let me explain this, why you pick up that stainless</line>
<line>'Cause your pops wasn't anxious to see you and you hate it</line>
<line>So much you probably had your burner tucked at graduation</line>
<topic type="violence"><line>So if you see him on 'em bleachers then you kill him</line></topic>
<line>Facing 25 to life with a murder charge</line>
<topic type="religion"><line>Your enemies was the prey and now you pray to God</line></topic>
<line>I pray these bars get farther than Compton</line>
<line>And if our record never break, I still won’t break my promise</line>
<line>I promise to keep it honest</line>
<line>Secret society, all we ask is trust</line>
<line>And all we lack is communication like service sucks</line>
<line>The people scared of annihilation when Kingdom Come</line>
<line>And I'm like, "The Kendrick Lamar OD in less than a month, all right?"</line>
<line>Gotta keep it pushing</line>
<line>Can't let the government tell me how my future looking</line>
<line>I'm on Rosecrans and Central trying to duck the central bookins'</line>
<line>If the fucking pigs get behind me then you know I'm bookin'</line>
<line>Never will I surrender</line>
<line>I been a warrior when I came out my mom's placenta</line>
<line>In the gutter lane like I'm Master Splinter</line>
<line>How splendid, I guess my project had did it</line>
<line>Got all these niggas approaching they mixtapes different</line>
<line>They said seven tracks, I said 15</line>
<line>Called it an EP, they said I’m trippin'</line>
<line>But little did they know, I’m tryna' change the rules</line>
<line>That we’ve been confined to, so the corporate won’t make decisions</line>
<line>Uppity bitches handling business</line>
<line>Killing our dreams, stealing our vision</line>
<topic type="social_issues"><line>Out in Haiti, adolescents barely have a home</line></topic>
<line>In LA everybody think they fucking on</line>
<line>Hop on Twitter, perpetrate we doing big shit</line>
<line>Who we hanging with and bragging about the iPhone</line>
<line>I swear to God most of y'all cats just don’t know Kendrick</line>
<line>You barely know yourself, so I guess most of y'all should be offended</line>
<topic type="wealth"><line>Ain’t doing this for my health, I’m tryna' purchase my momma dem' Benzes</line></topic>
<topic type="wealth"><line>Occupying my time with riches, justifying my time ambitions</line></topic>
<line>Just to coincide, just to go inside, plus we idolize why we living</line>
<line>Look, the mastermind took the master's mind</line>
<line>Just the perfect time, just to master mine</line>
<line>Just to match the grind with precision</line>
<line>Look, the mastermind took - <background>cough</background></line>
</verse>
 
<outro vocals="Alori_Joh" mood="null" tone="null">
<line>We would like to call this an appreciation tape for those who recognized the Kendrick Lamar EP. For this is the Kendrick Lamar OD. Because of you we are Overly Dedicated</line>
</outro>
</song>