<?xml-model href="../../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <artist>Kendrick Lamar</artist>
        <year>2017</year>
        <title>XXX</title>
        <featuredArtist>Bēkon, Kid Capri, Bono</featuredArtist>
        <album>DAMN.</album>
    </metadata>
    
<intro vocals="Bēkon Kid_Capri" mood="null" tone="null">
<line>America</line>
<line>God bless you if it's good to ya</line>
<line>America, please take my hand</line>
<line>Can you help me underst—</line>
<line>New Kung Fu Kenny!</line>
</intro>
    
<verse vocals="Kendrick_Lamar" mood="angry" tone="negative">
<line>Throw a steak off the ark to a pool full of sharks</line>
<line>He'll take it</line>
<topic type="violence"><line>Leave him in the wilderness with a sworn nemesis</line></topic>
<line>He'll make it <background>He'll make it</background></line>
<line>Take the gratitude from him, I bet he'll show you somethin'</line>
<line>Woah <background>Woah</background></line>
<line>I chip a nigga lil' bit of nothin'</line>
<line>I chip a nigga lil' bit of nothin'</line>
<line>I chip a nigga lil' bit of nothin'</line>
<line>I chip a nigga, then throw the blower in his lap</line>
<line>Walk myself to the court like, "Bitch, I did that!," X-rated</line>
<line>Johnny don't wanna go to school no mo', no mo'</line>
<line>Johnny said books ain't cool no mo' <background>No mo'</background></line>
<line>Johnny wanna be a rapper like his big cousin</line>
<line>Johnny caught a body yesterday out hustlin'</line>
<line>God bless America, you know we all love him</line>
<line>Yesterday, I got a call, like, from my dog, like 101</line>
<topic type="violence"><line>Said they killed his only son because of insufficient funds</line></topic>
<line>He was sobbin', he was mobbin', way belligerent and drunk</line>
<line>Talkin' out his head, philosophin' on what the Lord had done</line>
<topic type="religion"><line>He said: "K-Dot, can you pray for me? It been a fucked up day for me</line></topic>
<topic type="religion"><line>I know that you anointed, show me how to overcome."</line></topic>
<line>He was lookin' for some closure, hopin' I could bring him closer</line>
<line>To the spiritual, my spirit do know better, but I told him</line>
<line>"I can't sugarcoat the answer for you, this is how I feel:</line>
<topic type="violence"><line>If somebody kill my son, that mean somebody gettin' killed."</line></topic>
<line>Tell me what you do for love, loyalty, and passion of</line>
<line>All the memories collected, moments you could never touch</line>
<line>I wait in front a nigga's spot and watch him hit his block</line>
<line>I catch a nigga leavin' service if that's all I got</line>
<line>I chip a nigga, then throw the blower in his lap</line>
<line>Walk myself to the court like, "Bitch, I did that!"</line>
<topic type="social_issues"><line>Ain't no Black Power when your baby killed by a coward</line></topic>
<line>I can't even keep the peace, don't you fuck with one of ours</line>
<topic type="death"><line>It be murder in the street, it be bodies in the hour</line></topic>
<line>Ghetto bird be on the street, paramedics on the dial</line>
<topic type="family"><line>Let somebody touch my momma, touch my sister, touch my woman</line></topic>
<topic type="family"><line>Touch my daddy, touch my niece, touch my nephew, touch my brother</line></topic>
<line>You should chip a nigga, then throw the blower in his lap</line>
<line>Matter fact, I'm 'bout to speak at this convention, call you back—</line>
</verse>
 
<verse vocals="Kendrick_Lamar" mood="ambiguous" tone="neutral">
<line>Alright, kids, we're gonna talk about gun control</line>
<line><background>Pray for me</background> Damn!</line>
</verse>
    
<chorus vocals="Bono" mood="null" tone="null">
<line>It's not a place</line>
<line>This country is to me a sound</line>
<line>Of drum and bass</line>
<line>You close your eyes to look around</line>
</chorus>

<verse vocals="Kendrick_Lamar" mood="angry" tone="negative">
<topic type="religion"><line>Hail Mary, Jesus and Joseph</line></topic>
<topic type="violence"><line>The great American flag is wrapped in drag with explosives</line></topic>
<line>Compulsive disorder, sons and daughters</line>
<topic type="social_issues"><line>Barricaded blocks and borders—look what you taught us</line></topic>
<topic type="violence"><line>It's murder on my street, your street, back streets, Wall Street</line></topic>
<line>Corporate offices, banks, employees, and bosses with</line>
<topic type="violence"><line>Homicidal thoughts; Donald Trump's in office</line></topic>
<line>We lost Barack and promised to never doubt him again</line>
<line>But is America honest, or do we bask in sin?</line>
<line>Pass the gin, I mix it with American blood</line>
<topic type="social_issues"><line>Then bash him in, you Crippin' or you married to Blood?</line></topic>
<line>I'll aks again—oops, accident</line>
<line>It's nasty when you set us up then roll the dice, then bet us up</line>
<line>You overnight the big rifles, then tell Fox to be scared of us</line>
<line>Gang members or terrorists, et cetera, et cetera</line>
<line>America's reflections of me, that's what a mirror does</line>
</verse>

<chorus vocals="Bono" mood="null" tone="null">
<line>It's not a place</line>
<line>This country is to me a sound</line>
<line>Of drum and bass</line>
<line>You close your eyes to look ar—</line>
</chorus>
</song>