<?xml-model href="../../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
    <track>9</track>
        <artist>Tyler the Creator</artist>
        <year>2011</year>
        <title>Sandwitches</title>
        <featuredArtist>Hodgy</featuredArtist>
        <album>Goblin</album>
    </metadata>
    <intro vocals="Tyler_the_Creator" mood="angry" tone="negative">
        <line>Odd Future</line>
        <line>Wolf Gang</line>
        <line>They are them</line>
        <line>We are us</line>
        <topic type="violence"><line>Kill them all (Do it with me)</line></topic>
        <line>Wolf Gang, Wolf Gang, Wolf Gang, Wolf Gang, come on</line>
        <line>Wolf Gang, Wolf Gang, Wolf Gang, bitch, bitch over there in the yellow, come on</line>
        <line>Wolf Gang, Wolf Gang</line>
        <line>Say it loud!</line>
        <line>Like you mean it!</line>
        <line>Wolf Gang, Wolf Gang</line>
        <line>Nigga had the fucking nerve to call me immature</line>
        <line>Fuck you think I made Odd Future for?</line>
        <line>To wear fucking suits and make good decisions?</line>
        <line>Fuck that nigga, Wolf Gang</line>
    </intro>

    <verse vocals="Tyler_the_Creator" mood="angry" tone="negative">
        <line>Who the fuck invited Mr. I Don't Give a Fuck</line>
        <line>Who cries about his daddy in a blog because his music sucks? (I did!)</line>
        <line>Well, you fucking up, and truthfully I had enough</line>
        <line>And fuck rolling papers, I'm a rebel, bitch, I'm ashing blunts (Sorry)</line>
        <line>Full of shit, like I ate that john</line>
        <line>Come on kids, fuck that class and hit that bong</line>
        <topic type="violence"><line>Let's buy guns and kill those kids with dads and mom</line></topic>
        <line>With nice homes, 401ks, and nice ass lawns</line>
        <line>Those privileged fucks got to learn that we ain't taking no shit</line>
        <line>Like Ellen DeGeneres clitoris is playing with dick</line>
        <line>I'm jealous as shit, cause I ain't got no home meal to come to</line>
        <line>So, if you do, I'm throwing fingers out screaming "fuck you"</line>
        <line>I got ten of these Kennedy's</line>
        <topic type="violence"><line>Not Dom, but if I was a Dahm, I would be Jeffery</line></topic>
        <line>'Preme hat the color of a leprechaun with leprosy</line>
        <line>I'm fucking 'bout it, 'bout it, like I'm Master P in '96</line>
        <line>It's fucking immaculate, the way your daughter smacking dicks</line>
        <line>Surprised she hasn't taken gymnastic dick inside her alley-oop</line>
        <line>The Golf Wang hooligans is fucking up the school again</line>
        <line>And showing you and yours that breaking rules is fucking cool again</line>
        <line>I'm going harder than a midget jumping over me</line>
        <topic type="violence"><line>Chronic youth, I'm shoving blunt wraps in bitches ovaries</line></topic>
        <line>Punches to the stomach where that bastard kid supposed to be</line>
        <line>Fuck a mask, I want that ho to know it's me, ugh</line>
    </verse>
    <chorus vocals="Tyler_the_Creator" mood="angry" tone="negative">
        <line>Wolf Gang, Wolf Gang</line>
        <line>It's the Wolf Gang, Wolf Gang</line>
        <line>Wolf Wolf Gang, it's the Wolf Gang</line>
        <line>It's the Wolf Gang, Golf Wang</line>
        <line>It's the Wolf Gang, Wolf Gang</line>
        <line>Wolf Gang, triple six crew</line>
        <line>It's the Wolf Gang, Golf Wang</line>
        <topic type="violence"><line>Wolf Gang kill them</line></topic>
    </chorus>

    <verse vocals="Hodgy" mood="ambiguous" tone="neutral">
        <line>My love is gone for you mami, you could ride in hearses</line>
        <line>I'm sick in the brain dumb bitch, can you nurse this?</line>
        <line>You told me life would never, ever, ever get this perfect</line>
        <line>Then you smoke a J of weed, and take his kids to the churches</line>
        <line>Uh, fuck church, they singing and the shit ain't even worth it</line>
        <line>In the choir, whores and liars, scumbags and the dirt, bitch</line>
        <line>You told me God was the answer</line>
        <line>When I ask him for shit, I get no answer, so God is the cancer</line>
        <line>I'm stuck in triangles, looking for my angel</line>
        <line>Kill me with a chainsaw, and let my balls dangle</line>
        <line>Triple six is my number, you can get it off my Tumblr</line>
    </verse>

    <chorus vocals="Tyler_the_Creator" mood="angry" tone="negative">
        <line>Wolf Gang, Wolf Gang</line>
        <line>It's the Wolf Gang, Wolf Gang</line>
        <line>Wolf Wolf Gang, it's the Wolf Gang</line>
        <line>It's the Wolf Gang, Golf Wang</line>
        <line>It's the Wolf Gang, Wolf Gang</line>
        <line>Wolf Gang, triple six crew</line>
        <line>It's the Wolf Gang, Golf Wang</line>
        <topic type="violence"> <line>Wolf Gang kill them</line></topic>
    </chorus>
    <verse vocals="Hodgy" mood="ambiguous" tone="neutral">
        <line>It was hilarious, well it ain't fucking funny now</line>
        <line>I'll push this fucking pregnant clown into a hydrant stuck in the ground</line>
        <line>I step through the stomach, replace the baby with some fucking pounds</line>
        <line>"My baby daddy shoot bricks, the nigga also shoot rounds"</line>
        <line>Cause if I shoot blanks, oops, thanks</line>
        <line>I'm right back in it dead yummy and her mildew stank</line>
    </verse>

    <verse vocals="Tyler_the_Creator" mood="angry" tone="negative">
        <line>Free Earl, that's the fucking shit</line>
        <line>And if you disagree, suck a couple pimple-covered dicks</line>
        <line>Um, Wolf Gang, that's the fucking clique</line>
        <topic type="violence"><line>Golf Wang kill them all nigga, triple six</line></topic>
        <line>Fuck 2DopeBoyz, all them niggas bitches</line>
        <line>We don't need y'all, The Fader's who we really fucking with, bitch</line>
    </verse>

    <outro vocals="Tyler_the_Creator" mood="angry" tone="negative">
        <line>And we don't fucking make horrorcore, you fucking idiots</line>
        <line>Listen deeper than the music before you put it in a box, Wolf Gang</line>
    </outro>
</song>
