<?xml-model href="../../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <artist>Tyler the Creator</artist>
        <year>2011</year>
        <title>Goblin</title>
        <featuredArtist/>
        <album>Goblin</album>
        <trackNumber>1</trackNumber>
    </metadata>
    <intro vocals="Tyler_the_Creator" mood="anxious" tone="negative">
<line>You wouldn't do that Tyler, kill yourself or anyone. You don't even have the balls to begin with. What you need is me, someone to talk to, uh, it's been a while since our last session. So, tell me what's been going on</line>
    </intro>
    <verse vocals="Tyler_the_Creator" mood="angry" tone="negative">
<line>I'm not a fucking role model (I know this)</line>
<line>I'm a 19 year old fucking emotional coaster with pipe dreams</line>
<line>Since Kanye tweeted telling people he's bumping all of my shit</line>
<line>These mothafuckas think I'm 'sposed to live up to something? Shit</line>
<line>I'm still jacking off and proceeding my life careless</line>
<line>But getting more pussy 'cause I tell bitches I'm Wood Harris (as you should)</line>
<line>Philly to Paris, I'm getting these weird stares</line>
<line>At skateparks and airports all in a year, it's weird</line>
<line>Yonkers dropped and left them craniums mindfucked</line>
<line>Now competition missing like that nigga my mom fucked</line>
<line>He still hasn't called me yet (that's not your fault)</line>
<line>But that's a whole fucking different argument, shit, I got over it</line>
<line>And a couple bucks in my pocket, so now I could go buy</line>
<line>A couple Hot Pockets and grandma could stop cooking</line>
<line>Them nasty ass collard greens, pressure's on me like this top hat</line>
<line>Bastard intro, how the fuck I'm gonna top that?</line>
    </verse>

    <verse vocals="Tyler_the_Creator" mood="angry" tone="negative">
<line>"Tyler, you'll top it, you'll top that, you're a very capable individual"</line>
<line>"Okay, you guys caught me, I'm not a fucking rapist or serial killer, I lied"</line>
<line>"You know, you just want attention, you'll be fine"</line>
<line>"I try too hard, huh?"</line>
<line>"No, you don't"</line>
    </verse>
    <verse vocals="Tyler_the_Creator" mood="angry" tone="negative">
        <topic type="wealth"><line>Made a couple thou' and I just don't know what to buy yet</line></topic>
<line>The 'preme shit is free and I don't drink, so fuck a wine set</line>
<line>Nigga, fuck a mindset, my brain is an obscenity</line>
<line>I'm fucked in the head, I lost my mind with my virginity</line>
<line>Oh, that's a triple three six, isn't he a devil worshiper</line>
<line>Cause I'm too fucking ignorant to do some research?</line>
<line>I'm the star of the group (Yeah)</line>
<line>So no one else gets the respect that they deserve cause of you</line>
<line>(Bastard was good though) What you think I record it for?</line>
<line>To have a bunch a critics call my shit a bunch of horrorcore?</line>
<line>Like I didn't make "Parade" or "Inglorious"</line>
<line>Cause I'm too scared to tell my friends the way I really fucking feel?</line>
<line>Of course they only listen to lyrics about me pissin' off</line>
<line>In the tombs of Lara Croft, I'm getting pissed off (I bet)</line>
<line>Message boards are on my dick, I need a pissing waiver (here)</line>
<line>Let me bust one in they mouth, I know they full of flavor</line>
    </verse>

    <verse vocals="Tyler_the_Creator" mood="angry" tone="negative">
<line>"Can't they just be happy for me like, a kid with nothing, living out his dreams? Why they got to fucking hate?"</line>
<line>"I think everyone's happy, everyone's immature, everyone loves you Tyler, you have to believe that."</line>
<line>"I don't even skate anymore, I'm too fucking busy, I can barely kickflip now."</line>
<line>"Why? Why is that? Do you not have any free time when you're at home?"</line>
<line>"What the fuck you mean I'm not talented? You see the shit that I've been doing?"</line>
<line>"I have, I mean you're a great person."</line>
<line>"I mean, I'm not that great of a rapper but as a whole, I'm pretty cool, right?"</line>
    </verse>
    <verse vocals="Tyler_the_Creator" mood="angry" tone="negative">
<line>People excited, thinking shit is so tight (For what?)</line>
<line>Getting co-signs from rappers that I don't even like</line>
<line>What the fuck you want me to do? Start to gobble his mic?</line>
<line>And start Jackson him off until his cack blasting off? (No...)</line>
<line>Fuck that, (Yeah) These niggas ain't fucking with me</line>
<line>Cause I don't listen to the Immortal of Tech-of-the-nique</line>
<line>And all this underground bullshit that's never gon' peak</line>
<line>On the Billboard Top 20 and Jam of the Week</line>
<line>I'd rather listen to Badu and Pusha the T</line>
<line>And some Waka Flocka Flame instead (I love that shit) of that real hip hop</line>
<line>That's bull-of-the-sheet, but they want to critique</line>
<line>Everything that we, Wolf Gang, has ever released</line>
<line>But they don't get it, (They don't, it's not made for them) cause it's not made for them</line>
<line>The nigga that's in the mirror rapping, it's made for him</line>
<line>But they do not have the mindset that's same as him</line>
<line>I'm not weird, you're just a faggot, shame on him</line>
    </verse>

    <verse vocals="Tyler_the_Creator" mood="angry" tone="negative">
<line>"It is, but Tyler, you're going to have to cut down on that "faggot" word, that's very, that's a bad...</line>
<line>"I'm not homophobic."</line>
<line>"I mean, I don't think you are but..."</line>
<line>"Faggot."</line>
<line>"Alright, well, since the last time we..."</line>
<line>"The fuck is a good performance? I get on stage and I have as much fun as I can."</line>
<line>"I mean, you, you, it seems like you have fun. But your Twitter posts, just.. I mean, they're really random and it's ADD."</line>
<line>"Who doesn't have ADD..? Well, I don't."</line>
<line>"I mean, sometimes, you just say really outlandish things and we just want to know, what's the problem for this?"</line>
<line>"I wish Thebe was here."</line>
    </verse>
    <verse vocals="Tyler_the_Creator" mood="angry" tone="negative">
<line>Therapy's been sinning and niggas getting offended</line>
<line>They don't want to fuck with me cause I do not fuck with religion</line>
<line>You see, that's my decision, you fuckers don't have to listen</line>
<line>Here, put this middle finger in your ear (I'd rather not)</line>
        <topic type="violence"><line>When someone gets blamed cause some white kid had aimed (What?) his AK-47</line>
<line>At 47 kids, I don't wanna see my name mentioned</line></topic>
<line>(I don't think anyone's going to men—I don't think anyone takes you serious enough to believe you.)</line>
<line>College wasn't working and I wasn't working</line>
<line>So I was at home jerking off until my dick was hurting</line>
<line>But I was determined to be great, so those classes can wait</line>
<line>Cause the four days that I went, I wasn't learning shit (I mean, you...)</line>
<line>Now I'm living dreams that I wanted since eight</line>
<line>And can afford to get my mother something on her birthday</line>
<line>(I mean, you've explained to me that you were in school, but, I mean, I...)</line>
<line>They claim the shit I say is just wrong</line>
<line>Like nobody has those really dark thoughts when alone</line>
        <topic type="death"><line>I'm just a teenager, who admits he's suicide prone</line></topic>
<line>My life is doing pretty good, so that date is postponed for now</line>
<line>Wow, life's a cute bitch full of estrogen</line>
        <topic type="violence"><line>And when she gives you lemons, nigga, throw 'em at pedestrians</line></topic>
<line>(So, what are you saying, take advantage?</line>
<line>I mean, you've been doing pretty good, I've seen that)</line>
<line>I still live in my grandma's house</line>
<line>Sell out a fucking show in London just to end up on couches</line>
<line>I hate my fucking life, but when I make that announcement</line>
<line>My hero calls my phone, just to put that in doubt then</line>
<line>And then I am confused if I want in or just out</line>
<line>My friends really think I'm playing when I say I need counseling</line>
<line>I sit in grandmother's living room and just pout</line>
<line>And shout loud inside, sometimes I just want to die (No, you don't)</line>
<line>Odd Future came from the bottom</line>
<line>And it's gonna take a couple armed armies tryna stop 'em</line>
<line>(I believe you) All you fucking lames don't have to like me</line>
<line>The devil doesn't wear Prada, I'm clearly in a fucking white tee</line>
    </verse>

    <outro vocals="Tyler_the_Creator" mood="ambiguous" tone="neutral">
<line>Whoa, umm, alright, uh, so you was telling me you went to New York...</line>
    </outro>
</song>