<?xml-model href="../../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
    <track>2</track>
        <artist>Tyler the Creator</artist>
        <year>2021</year>
        <title>Corso</title>
        <featuredArtist>DJ Drama</featuredArtist>
        <album>Call Me If You Get Lost</album>
    </metadata>
    <intro vocals="Tyler_the_Creator DJ_Drama" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<line>You see (Uh)</line>
<line>On this here stage tonight is something legendary (Yo)</line>
<line>He goes by the name of The Creator (Crazy, ayo)</line>
<line>But you, you call him Tyler Baudelaire (Look)</line>
    </intro>

    <verse vocals="Tyler_the_Creator DJ_Drama" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<line>I be talkin' that fresh shit, I don't need gum (Nah)</line>
        <topic type="wealth"><line>Cookie crumbs in the Rolls, never no weed crumbs (No)</line></topic>
<line>He ain't talk to his bitch in three days</line>
<line>It ain't gotta be this way, I'm down for the threesome (Woo)</line>
        <topic type="wealth"><line>I might buy a boat (Nigga, yeah)</line></topic>
<line>Depends if Capri got space, don't really need one</line>
<line>I can go in the wintertime, baby, I bleed sun</line>
<line>Find another nigga like me 'cause I ain't seen one (Tell 'em, no)</line>
<line>Pull up in that, uh, whatchamacallit? (Nyoom)</line>
<line>Played a couple demos at Madison Square Garden</line>
<line>And tell them motherfuckers at Sony I'm not callin'</line>
        <topic type="wealth"><line>I'm plottin' on a billi', chilly in my garden, yuh</line></topic>
    </verse>

    <verse vocals="Tyler_the_Creator DJ_Drama" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<line>Alright</line>
<line>I admit it</line>
<line>We just been playin' with you niggas, man</line>
<line>T, I think you need to load that second clip</line>
<line>B-Hop, uh, French Waltz, uh</line>
        <topic type="wealth"><line>She say she like the Royce and I'm like "Which one?"</line>
<line>I got two, hun, look (Let's go)</line></topic>
<line>Catch me in my other-other-other-other crib, that's my AKA</line>
<line>Hurricane-proof all the views, shit like "A Bay Bay" (Damn)</line>
<line>The fuzzy hat, ascot, passport got tattoos</line>
<line>Slim nigga, big dick, with a fuckin' gap tooth</line>
<line>The way he beam (Bunny)</line>
<line>Call me Mr. Always On Some Shit You Never Seen (Hop)</line>
        <topic type="wealth"><line>In that mansion, livin' single, bitch, I'm Maxine</line></topic>
<line>"Niggas of your standard shouldn't talk"</line>
<line>Give a fuck about your thoughts, call me if you get lost, bitch</line>
    </verse>

    <verse vocals="Tyler_the_Creator DJ_Drama" mood="sad" tone="negative">
<line>Okay, now you understand what we came here to do, right?</line>
<line>Oh yeah, me, I go by the name of DJ Drama</line>
<line>And on my side, that's Tyler Baudelaire</line>
<line>AKA Bunnyhop</line>
<line>AKA The Creator</line>
<line>Call me if you get lost, suckers (Hahaha)</line>
<line>We didn't come to play wit' you niggas</line>

<line>Look, tried to take somebody bitch 'cause I'm a bad person</line>
<line>I don't regret shit because that **** worth it</line>
<line>In the end, she picked him, I hope when they fuckin'</line>
<line>She still thinkin' of me 'cause I'm that perfect</line>
<line>I'ma get that deep text when this verse surface</line>
<line>Better send it to my ego 'cause that shit hurtin'</line>
<line>Hope y'all shit workin' (True story), I'm a psycho, huh?</line>
<line>Don't give a fuck, you left my heart twerkin'</line>
<line>Movin', losin', grip on my doings (Yeah)</line>
        <topic type="wealth"><line>Eyes is cryin' on the jet cruisin' (Phew-phew-phew)</line></topic>
        <topic type="wealth"><line>'Bout to spend millions just to fill voids up</line></topic>
<line>Drama, I need you (Yessir), can you turn the noise up?</line>
<line>Can you turn the noise up? Can you turn the noise up? (Go, go, go, go)</line>
<line>Turn the fuckin' noise up, ah, nigga, my heart broken</line>
        <topic type="wealth"><line>Remembered I was rich, so I bought me some new emotions</line>
<line>And a new boat 'cause I'd rather cry in the ocean</line></topic>
<line>It's T, baby, uh</line>
    </verse>
    <outro vocals="Tyler_the_Creator DJ_Drama" mood="ambiguous" tone="neutral">
<line>Hahahaha, I tried to tell y'all</line>
<line>I don't even like using the word "bitch"</line>
<line>It just sounded cool</line>
    </outro>
</song>


