<?xml-model href="../../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <artist>Tyler the Creator</artist>
        <year>2021</year>
        <title>Lumberjack</title>
        <featuredArtist>DJ Drama</featuredArtist>
        <album>Call Me If You Get Lost</album>
    </metadata>
    <intro vocals="Tyler_the_Creator DJ_Drama" mood="hopeful" tone="positive">
        <topic type="wealth"><line>Rolls-Royce pull up, Black boy hop out</line></topic>
<line>Shoutout to my mother, and my father didn't— (Hold up)</line>
<line>"Oh, my God, I never seen nothin' like this"</line>
<line>Haha, that's what my mom was sayin'</line>
<line>She, she was cryin' and shit</line>
<line>It was, she was just like, "This shit is beautiful"</line>
<line>It was a beautiful moment</line>
<line>You alway– you always keep the picnic blankets in the back</line>
<line>'Cause you, you never know (Gangsta Grillz)</line>
<line>You never know where the fuck you gon' end up at</line>
<line>(Okay, haha, let's go, now we ready)</line>
    </intro>

    <chorus vocals="Tyler_the_Creator DJ_Drama Jasper" mood="angry" tone="positive">
        <topic type="wealth"><line>Rolls-Royce pull up, Black boy hop out</line></topic>
<line>Shoutout to my mother, and my father didn't pull out</line>
<line>MSG sell out, fuck these niggas yap 'bout?</line>
        <topic type="wealth"><line>Whips on whips, my ancestors got they backs out (Yeah, oh)</line></topic>
        <topic type="wealth"><line>Too far? Five hundred stacks for the hood (I dare you, nigga)</line></topic>
<line>Call me lumbеrjack 'cause I wish a nigga would race (Uh-huh, right)</line>
<line>Do it like I? This thе wish-a-nigga-could face (Uh)</line>
        <topic type="wealth"><line>They ain't gettin' paper like they should, wait</line></topic>
<line>(You niggas woulda, coulda, shoulda, oh, shit)</line>
    </chorus>

    <verse vocals="Tyler_the_Creator DJ_Drama Jasper" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<line>Niggas ain't really on the type of shit he on</line>
<line>I hit Drizzy and told him I had a milli' for him (Oh shit)</line>
        <topic type="wealth"><line>I own my companies full, told 'em to keep the loan</line></topic>
<line>I took that gold bitch home, niggas was big mad (Ugh, oh shit)</line>
<line>I put that bitch on the shelf to let it ventilate</line>
        <topic type="wealth"><line>And bought another car 'cause I ain't know how to celebrate (Top shelf, nigga)</line></topic>
<line>That big boy, that big bitch for all weather</line>
<line>It never rain in Cali', came with an umbrella (Ooh)</line>
    </verse>
    <chorus vocals="Tyler_the_Creator DJ_Drama Jasper" mood="confident" tone="positive">
        <topic type="wealth"><line>Rolls-Royce pull up, Black boy hop out (Man, what the fuck?)</line></topic>
<line>Shoutout to my mother, and my father didn't pull out</line>
<line>MSG sell out, fuck these niggas yap 'bout? (Sold out)</line>
        <topic type="wealth"><line>Good credit score, this card really can't max out (Wow)</line></topic>
        <topic type="wealth"><line>Too far? Five hundred stacks for the hood</line></topic>
<line>Call me lumberjack 'cause I wish a nigga would race (Uh-huh)</line>
<line>Nigga this the face, man I wish a nigg— (It's the face)</line>
<line>It's different, it's really different (Catch up, niggas)</line>
    </chorus>

    <verse vocals="Tyler_the_Creator DJ_Drama Jasper" mood="confident" tone="positive">
<line>Ayo, I might just sled in Utah, LA is too warm</line>
<line>My nigga tall, he look like a bitch, I call him Mulan (Hey, oh)</line>
<line>Salad colored emerald on finger, the size of croutons</line>
<line>Niggas can not fuck with performance of magic (Oh), new wand (Nigga)</line>
<line>That's my nuance, used to be the weirdo (Ah)</line>
<line>Used to laugh at me, listen to me with their ears closed</line>
        <topic type="wealth"><line>Used to treat me like that boy off Malcolm in the Middle (Why I'm motherfuckin' rich)</line></topic>
        <topic type="wealth"><line>Now I'm zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero (That's six)</line></topic>
    </verse>

    <outro vocals="Tyler_the_Creator DJ_Drama Jasper" mood="angry" tone="neutral">
        <topic type="wealth"><line>Rolls-Royce pull up (Zero), Black boy hop out (That's seven)</line></topic>
<line>Nah, I can't take this shit no more, man, I quit</line>
<line>That's it, I quit, I swear to God, nigga</line>
<line>Fuck niggas talking to me about? Close y'all fuckin' faces</line>
<line>Quality Wednesday music</line>
<line>Wish-a-nigga-could face</line>
<line>(Them stones is cloudy, nigga) Oh yeah, you asked for it</line>
<line>(Fuckin' crumbs) Wish-a-nigga-would face</line>
<line>Fuck you mean, nigga?</line>
    </outro>
</song>