<?xml-model href="../../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
    <track>4</track>
        <artist>Kanye West</artist>
        <year>2004</year>
        <title>All Falls Down</title>
        <featuredArtist>Syleena Johnson</featuredArtist>
        <album>The College Dropout</album>
    </metadata>
    <intro vocals="Kanye West" mood="energetic" tone="neutral">
        <line>I hear you, I hear you, L-Boogie</line>
        <line>Remember they used to call you that?</line>
        <line>What you say, Lauryn?</line>
        <line>You just keep singing, I'mma tell 'em</line>
        <line>Oh when it all, it all falls down</line>
        <line>I'm telling you all when it all falls down</line>
        <line><background>Oh when it all</background></line>
    </intro>

    <verse vocals="Kanye West" mood="empathetic" tone="negative">
        <line>Man I promise, she's so self conscious</line>
        <line>She has no idea what she doing in college</line>
        <line>That major that she majored in don't make no money</line>
        <line>But she won't drop out, her parents will look at her funny</line>
        <line>Now, tell me that ain't insecurr</line>
        <line>The concept of school seems so securr</line>
        <line>Sophmore three yurrs ain't picked a carurr</line>
        <line>She like fuck it, I'll just stay down hurr and do hair</line>
        <line>Cause that's enough money to buy her a few pairs of new Airs</line>
        <line>Cause her baby daddy don't really care</line>
        <line>She's so precious with the peer pressure</line>
        <line>Couldn't afford a car so she named her daughter Alexis</line>
        <line>She had hair so long that it looked like weave</line>
        <line>Then she cut it all off now she look like Eve</line>
        <line>And she be dealing with some issues that you can't believe</line>
        <line>Single black female addicted to retail and well</line>
    </verse>
    <chorus vocals="Kanye West" mood="sad" tone="negative">
        <line>Oh when it all, it all falls down</line>
        <line>Uh, and when it falls down who you gon' call now?</line>
        <line>Oh when it all, it all falls down</line>
        <line>C'mon c'mon, and when it falls down</line>
    </chorus>


    <verse vocals="Kanye West" mood="sad" tone="negative">
        <line>Man I promise, I'm so self-conscious</line>
        <topic type="wealth">
            <line>That's why you always see me with at least one of my watches</line>
            <line>Rollies and Pashas done drove me crazy</line>
            <line>I can't even pronounce nothing, pass that versace!</line>
            <line>Then I spent 400 bucks on this</line>
            <line>Just to be like, "Nigga, you ain't up on this!"</line>
            <line>And I can't even go to the grocery store</line>
            <line>Without some Ones that's clean and a shirt with a team</line>
            <line>It seems we living the American Dream</line>
        </topic>
        <line>But the people highest up got the lowest self-esteem</line>
        <line>The prettiest people do the ugliest things</line>
        <line>For the road to riches and diamond rings</line>
        <line>We shine because they hate us, floss cause they degrade us</line>
        <line>We trying to buy back our 40 acres</line>
        <line>And for that paper, look how low we a stoop</line>
        <line>Even if you in a Benz, you still a nigga in a coupe</line>
    </verse>

    <chorus vocals="Kanye West" mood="sad" tone="negative">
        <line>Oh when it all, it all falls down</line>
        <line>Uh, and when it falls down who you gon' call now?</line>
        <line>Oh when it all, it all falls down</line>
        <line>C'mon c'mon, and when it falls down</line>
    </chorus>
    <verse vocals="Kanye West" mood="sad" tone="negative">
        <line>I say fuck the police, that's how I treat 'em</line>
        <line>We buy our way out of jail, but we can't buy freedom</line>
        <line>We'll buy a lot of clothes but we don't really need 'em</line>
        <line>Things we buy to cover up what's inside</line>
        <line>Cause they make us hate ourself and love they wealth</line>
        <line>That's why shorties holler, "Where the ballers at?"</line>
        <topic type="drugs">
            <line>Drug dealer buy Jordan, crackhead buy crack</line>
        </topic>
        <line>And the white man get paid off of all of that</line>
        <line>But I ain't even gonna act holier than thou</line>
        <topic type="wealth">
            <line>Cause fuck it, I went to Jacob with 25 thou</line>
            <line>Before I had a house and I'd do it again</line>
            <line>Cause I wanna be on 106 and Park pushing a Benz</line>
            <line>I wanna act ballerific like it's all terrific</line>
        </topic>
        <topic type="poverty">
            <line>I got a couple past-due bills, I won't get specific</line>
            <line>I got a problem with spending before I get it</line>
        </topic>
        <line>We all self-conscious I'm just the first to admit it</line>
    </verse>


    <chorus vocals="Kanye West" mood="sad" tone="negative">
        <line>Oh when it all, it all falls down</line>
        <line>Uh, and when it falls down who you gon' call now?</line>
        <line>Oh when it all, it all falls down</line>
        <line>C'mon c'mon, and when it falls down</line>
    </chorus>

    <outro vocals="Kanye West" mood="confident" tone="positive">
        <line>Don't stop that shit, keep that shit</line>
        <line>Keep that part where I ran out of breath</line>
        <line>We ain't doing no punch-ins, man</line>
        <line>That's that fake shit</line>
        <line>If I was on stage, how I gotta spit it?</line>
        <line>It's from the heart anyway</line>
        <line>Might cause shortness of breath, ya know?</line>
        <line>Couldn't have got nobody better for the job</line>
        <line>Thank you very much this a beautiful</line>
        <line>Beautiful young lady that's inspired me definitely</line>
    </outro>

</song>
