<?xml-model href="../../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
    <track>20</track>
        <artist>Kanye West</artist>
        <year>2004</year>
        <title>Family Business</title>
        <featuredArtist/>
        <album>The College Dropout</album>
    </metadata>
    <intro vocals="?" mood="null" tone="null">
        <line>How's your son? <background>All the things</background></line>
        <line>He made the team this year? <background>All, all, all the things
            things</background></line>
        <line>Aight, they said he wasn't tall enough</line>
        <line><background>...all all that glitters is not gold</background></line>
        <line><background>And all gold is not reality</background></line>
        <line><background>Real is what you lays on me</background></line>
        <line>Ma we here we gon' cook this Sunday ok?</line>
        <line>That's your new girlfriend?</line>
    </intro>
    <verse vocals="Kanye West" mood="sad" tone="negative">
        <topic type="family">
            <line>This is family business</line>
            <line>And this is for the family that can't be with us</line>
            <line>And this is for my cousin locked down, know the answer's in us</line>
            <line>This why I spit it in my songs so sweet like a photo</line>
            <line>Of your granny's picture, now that you're gone, it hit us</line>
            <line>Super hard on Thanksgiving and Christmas, this can't be right</line>
            <line>Yeah, you heard the track I did man, "This Can't Be Life"</line>
            <line>Somebody please say grace so I can save face</line>
            <line>And have a reason to cover my face</line>
            <line>I even made you a plate, soul food, know how Granny do it</line>
            <line>Monkey bread on the side, know how the family do it</line>
            <line>When I brought it why the guard have to look all through it?</line>
            <line>As kids, we used to laugh</line>
            <line>Who knew that life would move this fast?</line>
            <line>Who knew I'd have to look at you through a glass?</line>
            <line>And look, you tell me you ain't did it, then you ain't did it</line>
            <line>And if you did, then that's family business</line>
        </topic>
    </verse>
    <chorus vocals="Kanye West" mood="sad" tone="negative">
        <line>And I don't care 'bout</line>
        <line><background>All the diamond rings, all the diamond rings</background></line>
        <line>They don't mean a thing <background>All, all, all the things</background></line>
        <line>All these fancy things</line>
        <line>I tell you that all is my weight and gold</line>
        <line><background>All that glitters is not gold, now gold is not reality</background></line>
        <line>Now all I know I know all these things</line>
        <line><background>Real is what you lease on me</background></line>
    </chorus>

    <verse vocals="Kanye West" mood="confident" tone="neutral">
        <topic type="family">
            <line>This is family business</line>
            <line>And this is for everybody standing with us</line>
            <line>Come on, let's take a family Grammy picture</line>
            <line>Abi, remember when they ain't believe in me?</line>
            <line>Now she like "See, that's my cousin on TV!"</line>
            <line>Now, we gettin' it and we gon' make it</line>
            <line>And they gon' hate it and I'm his favorite</line>
            <line>I can't deny it, I'm a straight rider</line>
            <line>But when we get together be electric slidin'</line>
            <line>Grandma, get 'em shook up</line>
            <line>Aw naw, don't open the photo book up</line>
            <line>I got an Aunt Ruth that can't remember your name</line>
            <line>But I bet them Polaroids'll send her down memory lane</line>
            <line>You know that one auntie, you don't mean to be rude</line>
            <line>But every holiday nobody eating her food</line>
            <line>And you don't wanna stay there cause them your worst cousins</line>
            <line>Got roaches at their crib like them your first cousins</line>
            <line>Act like you ain't took a bath with your cousins</line>
            <line>Fit three in the bed if it's six of y'all</line>
            <line>I'm talkin' 'bout three by the head and three by the leg</line>
            <line>But you ain't have to tell my girl I used to pee in the bed</line>
        </topic>
        <line>Rain, rain, rain go away</line>
        <line>Let the sun come out and all the children say</line>
        <line>Rain, rain, rain go away</line>
        <line>Let the sun come out and all the children say</line>
    </verse>

    <verse vocals="Kanye West" mood="happy" tone="positive">
        <line>I woke up early this morning with a new state of mind</line>
        <line>A creative way to rhyme without using knives and guns</line>
        <line>Keep your nose out the sky, keep your heart to God</line>
        <line>And keep your face to the risin' sun</line>
        <topic type="family">
            <line>All my niggas from the Chi, that's my family, dog</line>
            <line>And my niggas ain't my guys, they my family, dog</line>
            <line>I feel like one day you'll understand me, dog</line>
            <line>You can still love your man and be manly, dog</line>
            <line>You ain't got to get heated at every house warmin'</line>
            <line>Sittin' here, grillin' people like George Foreman</line>
            <line>Why Uncle Ray and Aunt Shiela always performin'?</line>
            <line>The second she storm out then he storm in</line>
            <line>Y'all gon' sit down, have a good time this reunion</line>
            <line>And drink some wine like Communion</line>
            <line>And act like everything fine and if it isn't</line>
            <line>We ain't letting everybody in our family business, uh</line>
        </topic>
    </verse>

    <chorus vocals="Kanye West" mood="sad" tone="negative">
        <line><background>All all all the diamond rings diamond rings</background></line>
        <line>They don't mean a thing <background>All, all, all the things</background></line>
        <line>They don't mean a thing <background>All, all, all the things</background></line>
        <line><background>All all that glitters is not gold, now gold is not
            reality</background></line>
        <line>They don't mean a thing a thing</line>
        <line><background>All, all, all the things</background></line>
        <line>They don't mean a thing a thing a thing</line>
        <line>I don't care what they don't mean a thing</line>
        <line><background>All, all, all the things</background> all these fancy things</line>
        <line>I tell you that all is my weight and gold</line>
        <line>All I know, I know all these things</line>
        <line>All these things, all these things</line>
        <line>All these things, all these things</line>
    </chorus>
    <outro vocals="Kanye West" mood="sad" tone="negative">
        <topic type="wealth">
            <line>CLK Mercedes Benz</line>
            <line>All these things, all these things ...</line>
            <line>All these things, all these things ...</line>
            <line>All these things, all these things ...</line>
            <line>A whole lotta money</line>
        </topic>
        <line>All these things, all these things</line>
        <line>All these things, all these things</line>
        <line>All these things, all these things</line>
        <topic type="family">
            <line>Mommy and Daddy, will you please stop fighting?</line>
        </topic>
        <line>All these things, all these things</line>
        <line>All these things, <background>And I don't care why</background> all these
            things</line>
        <line>All these things, all these things</line>
        <line>All these things, all these things...</line>
        <line>Let's get Stevie outta jail</line>
    </outro>
</song>
