<?xml-model href="../../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <metadata>
        <artist>Kanye West</artist>
        <year>2021</year>
        <title>Lord I Need You</title>
        <featuredArtist></featuredArtist>
        <album>Donda</album>
    </metadata>
<chorus vocals="Kanye West" mood="sad" tone="negative">
<topic type="religion"><line>Well, Lord, I need You to wrap Your arms around me</line>
<line>Wrap Your arms around with Your mercy</line>
<line>Lord, I need You to wrap Your arms around me</line>
<line>I give up on doin' things my way</line>
<line>And tell me everything's gonna be alright, oh</line></topic>
</chorus>
<verse vocals="Kanye West" mood="sad" tone="negative">
<topic type="love"><line>When you said give me a ring, you really meant a ring, huh?</line>
<line>Turned out to be more than just a fling, huh?</line>
<line>Three hours to get back from Palm Springs, huh?</line>
<line>Who you know spend an hour in Walgreens, huh?</line>
<line>You know you'll always be my favorite prom queen</line>
<line>Even when we in dad shoes or mom jeans</line>
<line>Too many complaints made it hard for me to think</line>
<line>Would you shut up? I can't hear myself drink</line>
<line>We used to do the freak like seven days a week</line>
<line>It's the best collab since Taco Bell and KFC, uh</line></topic>
<line>Talk to me nicely, don't come at me loud</line>
<line>You had a Benz at sixteen, I could barely afford a Audi</line>
<line>How you gon' try to say sometimes it's not about me?</line>
<line>Man, I don't know what I would do without me</line>
<line>Billionaire sport, step up to the court</line>
<line>They rented a room, we bought the resort</line>
<topic type="religion"><line>God got me, baby, God got the children</line>
<line>The devil run the playground, but God own the buildin'</line>
<line>Time and silence a luxury</line>
<line>Cussin' at your baby mama, guess that's why they call it custody</line>
<line>God got us, baby, God got the children</line>
<line>The devil run the playground, but God own the buildin'</line></topic>
<line>Time and space is a luxury</line>
<line>But you came here to show that you still in love with me</line>
<line>Startin' to feel like you ain't been happy for me lately, darlin'</line>
<line>'Member when you used to come around and serenade me, woah</line>
<line>But I guess it's gone different in a different direction lately</line>
<line>Tryna do the right thing with the freedom that you gave me <background>Wheezy outta here</background></line>
<line>Your gun off safety</line>
<line>Speak first, don't break me</line>
<line>Harsh words, you're angry</line>
<line>Lord, don't take me, oh, oh</line>
</verse>
<chorus vocals="Kanye West" mood="sad" tone="negative">
<topic type="religion"><line>Well, Lord, I need You to wrap Your arms around me</line>
<line>Wrap Your arms around with Your mercy</line>
<line>Lord, I need You to wrap Your arms around me</line>
<line>I give up on doin' things my way</line>
<line>And tell me everything's gonna be alright, oh <background>Wheezy outta here</background></line></topic>
</chorus>
</song>
