<?xml-model href="../../relax_ng.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
<intro vocals="Kanye West and Playboi Carti">
<line>What? Yeah</line>
<line>Boy <background>What?</background></line>
</intro>
<chorus vocals="Kanye West" mood="accomplished" tone="positive">
<line>We off the grid, grid, grid</line>
<line>This for my kid, kid, kid</line>
<line>For when my kid kid kids have kids</line>
<line>Everything we did for the crib</line>
</chorus>
<verse vocals="Kanye West" mood="accomplished" tone="positive">
<line>Everything we did, how we live <background>What?</background></line>
<line>All this smoke got a scent</line>
<line>All that smoke heaven sent <background>Scent</background></line>
<line>Everything I spoke, what I meant <background>Ah</background></line>
<line>Never disguise my intent, lines outside the event</line>
<line>Brought my life out the trench</line>
<topic type="religion"><line>God, thank God, look what He did, did, did, did, did, did</line></topic>
<line>We off the grid, grid, grid, grid, grid <background>Ayy</background></line>
<line>What?</line>
<line>We off the grid, grid, grid, grid</line>
</verse>
<verse vocals="Playboi Carti">
<line>I'm off the grid <background>Homicide, homicide, what?</background></line>
<line>Got tats on my ribs <background>Ah</background>, tattoos on my ribs <background>What?</background></line>
<line>I just tattеd my kid, Onyx <background>Slatt</background></line>
<line>I just threw twenty K on thesе ****, we was at Onyx <background>Ah, what?</background></line>
<line>I just bought me some brand new clothes, Dover Street Market <background>Givenchy</background></line>
<line>Ayy, we just took the route to Charlotte <background>Yeah, ah, what? Yeah</background></line>
<line>I'm in the Rolls-Royce **** on—what you call it? <background>Yeah, yeah</background></line>
<line>I light a opp blunt and let your **** try it <background>Ah</background></line>
<line>Uh, them off the grid, I'm on a **** diet <background>What?</background></line>
</verse>
<chorus vocals="Kanye West" mood="accomplished" tone="positive">
<line>We off the grid, grid, grid, grid</line>
<topic type="family"><line>This for my kid, kid, kid</line></topic>
<line>Everything we did for the crib did here</line>
<line>Flexin' with the business trip</line>
<topic type="mental health"><line>Going cray, take some G6</line></topic>
<line>Lit, lit, '76</line>
<line>He spit this</line>
<line>We off the grid, grid, grid</line>
</chorus>
<verse vocals="Fivio Foreign">
<line>Yeah, look, when I was in jail, I was lowkey <background>Uh</background></line>
<line>Shout out to supporters that wrote me</line>
<line>Eat food, work out and then go sleep</line>
<line>You know I'm prayin', he carryin' both feet <background>Yeah</background></line>
<line>**** know we got God with us <background>God with us</background></line>
<line>You look at me and see a God figure <background>Uh</background></line>
<line>And when I start vibin', I know that He with me</line>
<line>And I'ma always catch a hard shiver <background>Uh</background></line>
<line>I know it's demons in that dark liquor <background>Uh</background></line>
<line>We buy a bottle and squash with ya <background>Uh</background></line>
<line>Everybody turn into a harsh ****</line>
<line>But my pockets bigger and my heart richer <background>Uh</background></line>
<line>My mind smarter, my grind harder <background>Skrr</background></line>
<line>And my car quicker <background>Skrrt</background></line>
<line>I met her in church, she pray for me</line>
<line>She my God-sister <background>She my God-sister, yeah</background></line>
<line>I'm only trustin' the people I keep close</line>
<line>**** sellin' they soul for a repost</line>
<line>Remember when I was broke, wearin' cheap coats</line>
<line>Now it's diamonds and houses and C notes <background>Uh</background></line>
<line>****, I'm feelin' marvelous <background>I'm feelin' marvelous</background></line>
<line>Who let the monster loose? <background>Who let the monster loose? Huh</background></line>
<line>They call me a product of my environment <background>Uh</background></line>
<line>I tell them, "Nah, I'm what God produced" <background>Baow</background></line>
<line>Defense good, and them guards can shoot <background>Baow</background></line>
<line>I put 'em on you, it get hard to move</line>
<line>Tattoo in my face is the mark of truth</line>
<line>Gotta watch what you say when they market you <background>Huh</background></line>
<line>I already predicted this <background>I already predicted this, huh</background></line>
<line>Y'all only witnessed it <background>Y'all only witnessed it</background></line>
<line>Look, got a couple old friends that I'm not really clickin' with</line>
<line>I know they pray that we settle our differences</line>
<line>I pray that they lower all my **** sentences</line>
<line>I got some demons I'm not even dealin' with</line>
<line>They in they feelings, I'm not really feelin' it</line>
<line>And I know some members that gave back they membership</line>
<line>****, you switched up, huh, like how you not feelin' me?</line>
<line>Look, I act like I care, but I don't really care</line>
<line>Now I live in a new buildin' with amenities</line>
<line>I got a new ceilin' with a chimney</line>
<line>I got a few **** wanna finish me</line>
<line>I don't get too friendly with the enemy</line>
<line>You gotta move different when you in the industry, woo, yeah</line>
<line>You gotta move different when you in the industry, huh</line>
<line>You gotta move different when you in the, look</line>
<line>God blessed me with amazing grace <background>Uh</background></line>
<line>She fell in love with my day to day <background>Uh</background></line>
<line>I just want my problems to fade away <background>Uh</background></line>
<line>Man, I'm tired of ****, I need Gatorade</line>
<line>Boy, I got on my feet and I made a name</line>
<line>And I made it a necklace, huh</line>
<line>When you from the bottom and you workin' hard</line>
<line>Just to get to the top, then they gotta respect it</line>
<line>If you got a voice, then you gotta project it</line>
<line>If you got a wrong, then you gotta correct it</line>
<line>If you got a name, then you gotta protect it</line>
<line>If you give me shock, then you gotta electric <background>Woo</background></line>
<line>Tryna live a new life, so I got a new plan that I gotta finesse with <background>Look, yeah</background></line>
<line>'Cause they want me to lose, they ain't part of the Woos</line>
<line>I been tryin' so hard not to move reckless</line>
</verse>
<chorus vocals="Kanye West">
<line>We off the grid, grid, grid</line>
<line>This for my kid, kid, kid</line>
<line>Everything we did for the crib did here</line>
<line>Flexin’ with the business trip</line>
<line>Going cray, take some G6 <background>Ah</background></line>
<line>Lit, lit, '76</line>
<line>He split lids, then ask for shade, tsk-tsk-tsk</line>
<line>Take this trip, trip, trip, this, this</line>
<line>This, this, this, this</line>
<line>You all still lit, lit, lit</line>
<line>I'm off the grid, grid, grid, grid</line>
<line>Off the grid, grid, grid, grid</line>
</chorus>
<verse vocals="Kanye West" mood="angry" tone="">
<line>First, it go viral, then they get digital</line>
<line>Then they get critical, no, I'm not doin' no interview</line>
<line>Mask on my face, you can't see what I'm finna do</line>
<line>Had to move away from people that's miserable</line>
<line>Don't wanna link you, I ain't finna sit with you</line>
<line>Ain't finna talk to you, ain't finna get with you</line>
<line>Don't get me mad 'cause I don't wanna injure you</line>
<line>She put my paintings inside of her living room</line>
<line>Look at the problems and issues I'm livin' through</line>
<line>They tryna drown me, I rise to my pinnacle</line>
<line>Walked through the block like the neighborhood general</line>
<line>Drop me the lo' and then that's where I send it to</line>
<line>I was forgettin' you, now I remember, now I remember</line>
<line>Did what I want and I say what I want</line>
<line>And I thought you was with me, like how you get sensitive?</line>
<topic type="religion"><line>I got this God power, that's my leverages</line>
<line>I got this Holy Water, that's my beverages</line>
<line>I gotta help myself out of selfishness</line>
<line>I just bought a floor out of Selfridges</line>
<line>I gotta make sure they know who they messin' with</line>
<line>I gotta tell 'em "sorry," they too delicate</line>
<line>I gotta stay with God where the blessings is</line>
<line>I ain't deliverin' Heavenly messages just for the hell of it</line>
<line>Don't try to test me, I keep it clean, but it can get messy</line>
<line>I talk to God every day, that's my bestie</line></topic>
<line>They playin' soccer in my backyard, I think I see Messi</line>
<line>And this money could never neglect me</line>
<topic type="family"><line>I pray that my family, they never resent me</line></topic>
<topic type="love"><line>And she fell in love with me soon she met me</line></topic>
<topic type="money"><line>We both got a bag but my bag is more heavy</line>
<line>We had to stop countin', it's gettin' too petty</line>
<line>You not a real stepper, you can't overstep me</line>
<line>Just sit back and listen and watch how He bless me</line>
<line>He wait 'til I fall and then pull up and catch me</line>
<line>Your check is too small, you can't run up and check me</line></topic>
<line>Nah, nah, I get 'em fast, see</line>
<line>You feel a way, then go pull up and get me</line>
<line>Might do somethin' wild if I feel like you press me</line>
<line>Nah, I get 'em fast, see</line>
<line>You feel a way, then go pull up and get me</line>
<line>Might do somethin' wild if I feel like you press me</line>
</verse>
<chorus vocals="Kanye West" mood="accomplished" tone="positive">
<line>We off the grid, grid, grid</line>
<topic type="family"><line>This for my kid, kid, kid</line>
<line>For when my kid, kid, kids have kids</line></topic>
<line>Everything we did for the crib</line>
</chorus>
<outro vocals="Kanye West" mood="cynical" tone="negative">
<topic type="religion"><line>Pray for what folks and them did</line>
<line>Only thing we pray God forgive-give-give</line>
<line>May God forbid-bid-bid</line>
<line>He hit one of the kids, kids, kids</line>
<line>Took off His list, list, list</line>
<line>Look what they did, did, did</line>
<line>Pray for the crib, crib, crib</line>
<line>Some say A-A-Adam could never be bla-a-ack</line>
<line>'Cause a black man'll never share his rib, rib, rib, rib, rib, rib</line></topic>
</outro>
</song>